<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Sentences>
<sentence id="0">
<text>
I am a year away from completing my BS in Human Service Management and will continue on to my Masters in Psychology - all at UoP.
I'm giving it 4 out of 5 because I have not completed the course as of yet.
As of now I am going to a campus and would like to keep it that way.

There are pro's and con's to every and any school that you go to.
I ma only echoing what others have said in these posts.
As of now, I have had only one instructor who - although I liked him as a person - I felt maybe could have done a bit more as far as joining in the class.
The course material I feel is sufficient and I've yet to have any real problem with people in my team.
That's not to say that there haven't been the occassional bad apple - there has been - but for those of you you have been in a team you know that when you set up you team charter you also lay down the team rules.

With this school you get out of it what you put into it - like anything you do in life.

I am a working adult and am newly married so this school works for me, and when the wife decides when she wants to start having children I will be thankfull for this school.
I've never - let me repeat - NEVER had a problem with the faculty.
Everytime I've needed something from them they've been right on top of it.

Again - I have no regrets.
If you go in with a foul attitude your experience will reflect that.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1252" end="1260" value="they've"/>
<opinion start="1265" end="1278" value="right on top" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="563" end="579" value="course material"/>
<opinion start="581" end="586" value="feel" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="887" end="894" value="school"/>
<opinion start="898" end="933" value="get out of it what you put into it" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="142" end="145" value="it"/>
<opinion start="145" end="156" value="4 out of 5" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1011" end="1023" value="this school"/>
<opinion start="1023" end="1029" value="works" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="245" end="276" value="would like to keep it that way" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="1">
<text>
I do not know the quality of the education at this school.
I am sure it is fine as it is self paced and you get what you are willing to put in to it, I suspect.
However, the people that do the admissions need lots of training.
They are very nice people until you deviate from what they want you to do.
Then they become abusive.
I literally was screamed at and hung up on.
Screamed at isn't like spoken to in an angry voice.
Screamed at like at the top of your lungs, like a little child having a tantrum.
After complaining to someone named Matt Veril who said, he was sorry if I was upset but wasn't &quot;there&quot; when it happened so couldn't say anything about it.. uh hello?
I haven't ever met a supervisor that would take the side of a badly behaving employee.
Sounds to me like it is a tactic they use.
Because not one but two different departments tried to strong arm me.
I think the school probably is a good one, but they need to come up with a different way to admit people.
The way it is now, they wont keep many clients.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="232" end="237" value="They"/>
<opinion start="246" end="251" value="nice" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="313" end="318" value="they"/>
<opinion start="325" end="333" value="abusive" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="197" end="208" value="admissions"/>
<opinion start="208" end="230" value="need lots of training" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="903" end="910" value="school"/>
<opinion start="924" end="929" value="good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="765" end="774" value="employee"/>
<opinion start="750" end="765" value="badly behaving" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="2">
<text>
To lifeisgoodoutthere: I've just reported you to the administrative area of RateItAll...AGAIN!
May I point out to you the message on the top of the screen that states that &quot;All reviews off topic will be removed, as well as those that challenge the integrity of other reviewers&quot;.To
other readers and potential reviewers out there, please be patient while RateItAll works this problem out.
This person has just had numerous reviews yanked off of this site just last week because they refuse to be civil and respectful of anothers viewpoint and experiences with Capella.
This person also has numerous aliases so watch out for their reviews.
The site will find them all and take away their right to post if they keep it up.
</text>
</sentence>
<sentence id="3">
<text>
UOP is a good school either online or going to the ground campus.
Of course it is not as good as NorthWestern or Harvard but this is a different kind of school.
This is a college desgined to help adults who are already employed full-time who do not have the time to go to a traditional school.
The classes are tailored so these students can still learn and earn their degrees.
The class material is just as indepth and challenging as I have taken at the University of Illinois and far more challenging than my local community college.
The majority of the complaints have been about counselors or financial aid as well as strong selling tactics.
This is all true but the goal of students is to get a good education an to earn a degree.
If you go out to eat and have bad service or if you buy a car and hate the hassel the salesman does that mean that your food was bad or that the car you bought was bad?
No, it means parts of the process were not desireable but the end product was good.
UOP has instructors who are all working in their field right now, they are in the mix everyday and pass along this information to students.
The material is not week nor is the work load requirements from the students.
I am almost finished with my degree and I feel that the education I have earned has been just as good as when I went to U of I. Dont let people tell you it is a degree mill, it is not!
These people have not taken classes at UOP and are making blanket statements about UOP just because it is not a traditional school.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1144" end="1153" value="material"/>
<opinion start="1160" end="1165" value="week" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="77" end="80" value="it"/>
<opinion start="87" end="98" value="as good as" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="385" end="400" value="class material"/>
<opinion start="403" end="419" value="just as indepth" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1275" end="1285" value="education"/>
<opinion start="1308" end="1324" value="just as good as" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="0" end="4" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="9" end="14" value="good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="163" end="168" value="This"/>
<opinion start="181" end="190" value="desgined" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="1407" end="1420" value="These people"/>
<topic start="1490" end="1494" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="1458" end="1484" value="making blanket statements" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1395" end="1398" value="it"/>
<opinion start="1381" end="1393" value="degree mill" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="4">
<text>
The education system is top range BUT administration, IT and finance are quite messy though.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="38" end="70" value="finance IT administration"/>
<opinion start="80" end="86" value="messy" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="14" end="21" value="system"/>
<opinion start="24" end="34" value="top range" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="5">
<text>
I can say that studying in the University of Phoenix Online has been a great experience.
The professor are very experienced and I have learned a lot.
I am two classes away to finish my Master's Degree.
Thanks!
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="113" end="125" value="experienced" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="31" end="53" value="University of Phoenix"/>
<opinion start="77" end="88" value="experience" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="6">
<text>
Hello... First, I am a Capella PhD student who is about done!!
My dissertation is currently in the committee approval and is about to be turned into the school for approval!
With that said...for those who are questioning the validity of Capella, you will have to make your own mind up, but from my experience...it is no joke.
I have felt like giving up before, but the school of B and Tkept pushing me.
The dissertation process was the hardest thing that I have ever done, mentally (and I have done several demanding tasks in the US Army).
It wasn't hard from the &quot;Capella sucks&quot; mindset...but from the &quot;you can't just walk in there, pay your money, and get your degree&quot; mindset.
For those who have that mindset about Capella, you need to be put away for insanity (or for frivolous motivations).
Do I ever feel that I have to defend my degree (or soon to be degree)?
Sure.
Why?
Because all of the nut jobs out that that have zero clue what distance education is about and their failures on life in general.
I, like I said, am a veteran.
Mom and dad couldn't pony up for me to go off to school right out of HS (not that there is anything wrong with that just making a point).
When I got out of the Army, I had started a family and a career, so the act of going to school (even part time) was hard.
But I did it with my BS and MS.
Something that I have learned about these people with pessimism towards Capella is that they are on tilt, have had their &quot;wittle&quot; feelings hurt by the process, or just are down right mad/ jealous that there are other options than the traditional B and M route (of which my BS and MS are from B and M schools).
With all that praise said, and to show my non-partisanship towards Capella, I will state that I feel they over advertise on mediums such as the Internet, which brings down the &quot;shine&quot; in a sense.
Also, they do need to start putting forth some more stringent standards on acceptance...i.e...GMAT scores, etc.
AND of course the cost...it isnt cheap!
Just MHO.
Oh...almost forget....for the &quot;Einstein&quot; that made the idiotic remark that people that go/ graduate from Capella have no real world experience...
Dude, get a clue!
I have active duty military experience, collegiate teaching experience, and over 10 years of professional IT experience.
You can take your foot out of your mouth at any time :)
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="707" end="713" value="those"/>
<topic start="741" end="749" value="Capella"/>
<opinion start="727" end="735" value="mindset" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="244" end="252" value="Capella"/>
<opinion start="216" end="228" value="questioning" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="2092" end="2101" value="Einstein"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="2194" end="2205" value="experience" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1794" end="1799" value="they"/>
<opinion start="1789" end="1794" value="feel" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="419" end="432" value="dissertation"/>
<opinion start="448" end="456" value="hardest" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="1416" end="1423" value="people"/>
<topic start="1446" end="1454" value="Capella"/>
<opinion start="1428" end="1438" value="pessimism" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1900" end="1905" value="they"/>
<opinion start="1946" end="1966" value="stringent standards" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="566" end="571" value="hard" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="7">
<text>
For all you non-students who keep writing these negitive reviews, before you write these trash do your research.
An online degree takes dedication and self motivation.
Yes the advisors are sales persons, but guess what if it takes a sales person to get me off my ass to make an improvement in my life then go ahead.
I am a current CTU international student.
No let me rewrite that.
&quot;I AM A PROUD INTERNATIONAL CTU STUDENT&quot;.
For most CTU is just another college they and jump from like a froh would a lilly pod.
try and committ to one school and no matter how hard the course work is.
I love CTU and will continue from there all the way to my masters.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="603" end="607" value="CTU"/>
<opinion start="598" end="603" value="love" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="418" end="422" value="CTU"/>
<opinion start="398" end="404" value="PROUD" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="438" end="443" value="most"/>
<topic start="443" end="447" value="CTU"/>
<opinion start="450" end="463" value="just another" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="179" end="188" value="advisors"/>
<opinion start="188" end="206" value="are sales persons" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="125" end="132" value="degree"/>
<opinion start="132" end="149" value="takes dedication" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="8">
<text>
I just recently enrolled with UOP online, this would be my first experience attending an online course.
At first i was a bit apprehensive, but onc i got started it seems pretty simple.
I was not aware of so many horrible opinions of the university.
Which have me questionging if i had made a mistake.
Yes it is extrememly expensive, almost three times more than what i was paying per credit hour, so much that the military tuition cannot cover all of it.
I have noticed when contacting my councelor it is hard to get a hold of them, and when i leave voice mails i never receive phone calls back.
One issue that extremely disturbed me was just recently i received an email stating there was an error in my paper work and that i could not be matriculated (i find this out now two weeks into my class).
I contacted the finance office the person on the other end was short, and pointless with responses to my answers (i am beginning to wonder).
I have gathered the impression of the people in class as being fools.
It seems most of them are on there to get by and pay for their degree.
It sounds exspensively convinient, but it does not work for me when i need to IMPLEMENT my skills.
I am going to continue in my undergraduate program and continue to carefully examin the quality of my experience at UOP online.
For now i have had a somewhat decent experience, concerning at one point but decent for the moment.
More posts to come.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="997" end="1004" value="people"/>
<opinion start="979" end="990" value="impression" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1047" end="1052" value="them"/>
<opinion start="1033" end="1039" value="seems" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1142" end="1145" value="it"/>
<opinion start="1154" end="1159" value="work" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="830" end="845" value="finance office"/>
<opinion start="877" end="883" value="short" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="164" end="167" value="it"/>
<opinion start="173" end="187" value="pretty simple" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="9">
<text>
I am enrolled at CTU Online in thier Masters of Science/Management program.
I am about 75% through the program.
I attended a 2 year and a 4 year brick-and-mortar college to get my Associates and Bachelor's degree.
My experience so far has been positive.
I have only had 1 instructor that was out of his league.
He had only recently entered the IT field and had had his PhD less than 2 years.
He had no practical knowledge of the subject - only textbook knowledge.
After a few conversations with my accademic advisor, the professor was referred to the dean for counseling.
All student's work was submitted to another professor for grading.
The coursework is mostly research papers.
The textbooks help with the foundation and basics of the class, and the research papers help you to expand on that knowledge.
The online class time is bennificial to those not already familiar with the subject matter.
However, those of us that have been in the business environment for a few years can skip the live chat and skim over the transcripts to see if any interesting discussions were held.
Overall, I feel that this program is a good choice for those of us that do not have the time to attend a traditional college and that have put in a few years of work in the business sector.
However, I would not reccomend this to those fresh out of high school, or those who have never held a job.
As far as the high tuition, all online colleges are expensive.
CTU's tuition and fees are in-line with other online colleges that I researched.
The same degree at a brick-and-mortar college would have cost me about $5K less, but I would have had to go longer and drive an hour one way to attend class.
Overall I give CTU a B-.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1142" end="1149" value="choice"/>
<opinion start="1137" end="1142" value="good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="220" end="231" value="experience"/>
<opinion start="247" end="256" value="positive" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="696" end="706" value="textbooks"/>
<opinion start="706" end="711" value="help" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1418" end="1426" value="tuition"/>
<opinion start="1413" end="1418" value="high" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="276" end="287" value="instructor"/>
<opinion start="296" end="314" value="out of his league" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="781" end="786" value="help" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1721" end="1725" value="CTU"/>
<opinion start="1727" end="1730" value="B-" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="824" end="842" value="online class time"/>
<opinion start="845" end="857" value="bennificial" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="10">
<text>
I am a student in the healthcare management program and it has proved at times to be very intense and difficult, Especially if you also work 50, or for those who work 40 hours, or more a week.
I have also learned a lot.
Some have had good experiences and some have had bad, don't discount UOP if you don't know anything about it.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="56" end="59" value="it"/>
<opinion start="90" end="98" value="intense" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="295" end="299" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="286" end="295" value="discount" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="56" end="59" value="it"/>
<opinion start="102" end="112" value="difficult" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="11">
<text>
It shocks me that half of the people that degrade this college can hardly type a crappy review without misspellings, errors and just plain stupidity.
Maybe it has nothing to do with your &quot;personal experiences&quot;, maybe you ought to look beyond your crappy day at the student finances office.
As I read through each and everyone of these reviews, the negatives leaned towards stating the exact same crap, while the positives actually made some valid points (while still including a few negatives).
It surprises me that most of you could even pass the CPT, and if you didn't then yes, you are going to learn some remedial crap.
That's the name of the game.
As for everyone that makes a point to say how &quot;Devry is only out for the money&quot;, and I'm forced to paraphrase, since most of these comments were spelled wrong, WELCOME TO COLLEGE.
Do you think that any university is not there for the money?
Do you think any teacher is not there for the money?
Do you think the people that work at Yale wake up and say, &quot;Hey, I can't wait to help some students&quot;?
You are sadly mistaken.
College is about money or it would be free, just like public high schools.
Devry has had an incredible impact on me, and I can only hope that I succeed and graduate.
Maybe if you cracked one of those &quot;over-priced&quot; books once in awhile, you would see that Devry has quite a bit to offer.
I will tell you, I have not seen a price for ONE book that has not been equivalent to the price of books at the community college I attended.
A community college.
Yes, you are thinking what do I know, I only attended a community college.
Well, I may not have experience when it comes to different colleges, but maybe that is your flaw.
Pick something.
Don't crap-talk a school, that I'm sure half of you have either flunked out of, or realized early on that you couldn't cut it in, just because your angry.
I have not once had a problem contacting anyone that I needed to contact.
Maybe you have, but does that mean that the hundred people to your one (by this I mean you, for the slow folks) that HAVE been helped have experienced the same problems?
Try stepping out beyond yourself and look at the bigger picture.


I don't even know why I felt compelled to post, but you all have successfully angered me.
Devry is an incredibly competent school that has taught me more in my first two semesters, than I have learned from 23 years of life.
I'm elated that I was able to experience Devry and cannot wait until I graduate.
Good luck to you and your upper-level management position at Pizza Hut, I hope you prosper.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="30" end="37" value="people"/>
<topic start="55" end="63" value="college"/>
<opinion start="42" end="50" value="degrade" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="2503" end="2509" value="Devry"/>
<opinion start="2466" end="2473" value="elated" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1364" end="1370" value="Devry"/>
<opinion start="1380" end="1395" value="a bit to offer" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="247" end="252" value="your"/>
<topic start="270" end="294" value="student finances office"/>
<opinion start="252" end="259" value="crappy" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="1281" end="1285" value="you"/>
<topic start="1322" end="1328" value="books"/>
<opinion start="1308" end="1320" value="over-priced" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1948" end="1959" value="contacting"/>
<opinion start="1940" end="1948" value="problem" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="2326" end="2332" value="Devry"/>
<opinion start="2349" end="2359" value="competent" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1207" end="1214" value="impact"/>
<opinion start="1196" end="1207" value="incredible" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="12">
<text>
I am a recent graduate with a Master's degree from Capella University.
There is no doubt in my mind that an education from Capella is a high-quality one.
Every single course I took was challenging and educational (I took four years worth of courses, having changed my focus throughout that time).
The requirements and demands are rigorous.
There is barely a time throughout each course in which you feel you can just slow down; be thankful for your two-week break between each course!
I'll admit that before beginning my education at Capella, I did not think online learning would be that difficult; in fact, I think I assumed it WOULD be easy.
I was wrong; I assure you, online learning at Capella was the most difficult form of education I have undergone!
It is almost completely self-learning; and to those of you who are &quot;unlearned&quot; in the art of self-learning, there is nothing passive or lazy about it.
By the end of each course, I would look back at the coursework I completed, and would be so amazed at the ground covered and the knowledge gained.
Is everything perfect, all of the time?
Well, what can you say IS?
As far as quality education, they do not skimp.
Most instructors are very involved and available; and you interact more with peers than what might be required in traditional brick and mortar.
I will say, I often did miss the physical interactions that a brick and mortar education offers; and you do have to be prepared for the &quot;silence&quot; (which, by the way, was maddening to me at first).
But you do adapt; and I was actually quite thankful that I could attain such a thorough education in the comfort of my own home.
Online learning, if one has not done it, brings up a few misconceptions among people.
Talk to those who HAVE done it before you make a decision.
Blessings!
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1206" end="1218" value="instructors"/>
<opinion start="1227" end="1236" value="involved" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="109" end="119" value="education"/>
<opinion start="137" end="150" value="high-quality" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1487" end="1495" value="silence"/>
<opinion start="1524" end="1534" value="maddening" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="84" end="90" value="doubt" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="169" end="176" value="course"/>
<opinion start="187" end="199" value="challenging" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1181" end="1186" value="they"/>
<opinion start="1193" end="1199" value="skimp" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1181" end="1186" value="they"/>
<opinion start="1161" end="1169" value="quality" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="386" end="393" value="course"/>
<opinion start="356" end="363" value="barely" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1083" end="1094" value="everything"/>
<opinion start="1094" end="1102" value="perfect" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="727" end="737" value="difficult" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="903" end="919" value="passive or lazy" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="307" end="332" value="requirements demands"/>
<opinion start="336" end="345" value="rigorous" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="569" end="585" value="online learning"/>
<opinion start="563" end="609" value="think online learning would be that difficult" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="13">
<text>
I just finished my Bachelor of Science/Business Management at UOP and I am now getting ready to start the MBA program at UOP.
I started as a junior having gone to community college prior.
The 22 months that it took me on ground were the best times of my life.
The Sacramento Valley campus has some of the most remarkable instructors I have ever had.
I have 18 years of work experience in my field and the learning environment that University of Phoenix provides is far more relative to business than a traditional college.
The students not only have to learn to work together in teams, but also learn how to present learned material.
The students get the opportunity to be good at public speaking.
Compared to the traditional &quot;cram for exams&quot;, the UOP student must learn the material enough to present in front of the class; not to mention the many, many research papers that are required in each of the courses.
As a hiring manager, I would lean more toward someone with a degree from University of Phoenix than one from a state university.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="435" end="457" value="University of Phoenix"/>
<opinion start="478" end="487" value="relative" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1001" end="1023" value="University of Phoenix"/>
<opinion start="957" end="967" value="lean more" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="759" end="771" value="UOP student"/>
<opinion start="771" end="795" value="must learn the material" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="324" end="336" value="instructors"/>
<opinion start="313" end="324" value="remarkable" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="209" end="212" value="it"/>
<opinion start="235" end="261" value="the best times of my life" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="645" end="654" value="students"/>
<opinion start="680" end="685" value="good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="14">
<text>
The University of Phoenix online is a joke.
Returning students who need an online program should do everything in their power to find a different school.
It's an exception to find a UOP instructor who is fully competent.
Standards between &quot;facilitators&quot; (they don't like to call them instructors or professors at UOP) are practically non-existent.
Class syllabuses are dictated by the University, and instructors frequently use this as an excuse for a poor class.
The &quot;Learning Team&quot; element (which is intrinsic to every class and accounts for 40-60% of your grade) is nothing by a crapshoot.
If you are a good student, you will usually (not always, but usually) doing 80-100% of the &quot;team&quot; assignments yourself if care about getting an A in the class.
Online quizzes and tests are often very badly written, and I have yet to have a single instructor who was willing to say &quot;yeah, that wasn't the best way to ask that question.&quot;
Unlike all modern universities, there is no way to get feedback on an instructor before you are financially committed to the class.
Unlike normal universities, you don't even get a choice of instructors -- the instructor is assigned the day before your class starts.
Once you make even a single post to the class newsgroup you are financially committed to that class (I don't know if this is rigidly enforced).


Bottom line: there are a lot of online degree programs available now -- don't waste you time and money with UOP.
And, BTW, just in case you think this is a &quot;sour grapes&quot; rant -- I'm less than a year away from my degree and still have a 4.0 GPA.
This is just flat out a bad school.
I wish I'd never started the program.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="794" end="800" value="tests"/>
<opinion start="815" end="829" value="badly written" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="4" end="26" value="University of Phoenix"/>
<opinion start="38" end="43" value="joke" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1634" end="1661" value="school just"/>
<opinion start="1650" end="1654" value="bad" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="224" end="234" value="Standards"/>
<opinion start="341" end="354" value="non-existent" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1692" end="1700" value="program"/>
<opinion start="1665" end="1670" value="wish" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="1447" end="1468" value="don't waste you time" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="184" end="199" value="UOP instructor"/>
<opinion start="212" end="222" value="competent" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="478" end="496" value="" Learning Team ""/>
<opinion start="583" end="606" value="nothing by a crapshoot" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="15">
<text>
I have just completed my first set of courses in my undergraduate degree at Capella University.
I have to say that Capella University truly holds to quality education as well has helping learn new business skills to be effective in my career.
Not to mention their customer service is second to none and I am truly appreciative of online education.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="158" end="168" value="education"/>
<opinion start="150" end="158" value="quality" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="116" end="135" value="Capella University"/>
<opinion start="286" end="301" value="second to none" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="16">
<text>
i just applied for devry university online and i am concerned with the entrance exam!
what is the entrance exam like, how can i study for it?
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="71" end="85" value="entrance exam"/>
<opinion start="52" end="62" value="concerned" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="17">
<text>
If a CTU recruiter contacts you... RUN!
Their Software Engineering Program is about $32,000 shy of being a diploma mill .
Their recruiters make the following promises: we provide the textbooks as a part of the tuition, wonderful instructors, great online interactive learning environment, online library, online resource, but worst of all they tell you that the program is specifically for students that are completely new to programming.
AND that you will qualify for a job as a programmer upon graduation.
LIES!
The free books taht they provide are so poor in quality you cannot even find their isbn's on the internet.
Not to mention, the books do not cover the required material necessary to complete the assignments.
It is impossible to be successful at this university or to learn everything.
There are students in the very first programming class and even after taking this class twice they cannot write a single line of code.
However, they finish the class with an A!!!! If you are already a programmer and just want a degree, this is the university for you.
But if you want to learn something... stay away and go someplace that provides students with the tools necessary to get jobs when they graduate.
Please someone tell me how this school received a regional accreditation!
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="779" end="790" value="university"/>
<opinion start="743" end="754" value="impossible" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="575" end="583" value="quality"/>
<opinion start="567" end="572" value="poor" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="235" end="295" value="instructors  learning environment"/>
<opinion start="520" end="525" value="LIES" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="132" end="143" value="recruiters"/>
<topic start="235" end="247" value="instructors"/>
<opinion start="225" end="235" value="wonderful" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="111" end="124" value="diploma mill" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="349" end="354" value="they"/>
<opinion start="336" end="342" value="worst" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="132" end="143" value="recruiters"/>
<topic start="274" end="295" value="learning environment"/>
<opinion start="249" end="255" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="18">
<text>
I'm going to Valdosta U in GA.
Your courses get called off too many times.
I don't know how those 52 admirals and generals yu all brag about ever got a UMUC degree since your courses get called off so often.
Oh yeah, I wasn't too crazy about the quality of your professors.
UMUC was much better 3 or 4 year ago, but those people have moved on to better lives, better jobs, or whatever.
My last UMUC course did not meet the course description and goals, and it was a second choice bcause the first choice got called off.
I don't want to take your DE courses, and don't like being pushed in that direction.
See you in Valdosta!
My friends say it's pretty good there.
Steve, Germany.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="37" end="45" value="courses"/>
<opinion start="60" end="69" value="too many" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="266" end="277" value="professors"/>
<opinion start="223" end="240" value="wasn't too crazy" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="403" end="415" value="UMUC course"/>
<opinion start="423" end="428" value="meet" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="279" end="284" value="UMUC"/>
<opinion start="293" end="300" value="better" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="125" end="128" value="yu"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="132" end="137" value="brag" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="19">
<text>
All that have went to CTU are dumb for not doing there homework and research.Stick to a goverment backed school like your community college or local University!Your
degrees are fake, they will not be respected by any legtimate employer that requires real education!The cat is out of the bag, with respect to the goverment investigations listed below.
CEC, Colorado Technical University's parent company, is currently being investigated by the Securities Exchange Commission (The Federal Goverment) [1] the United States Postal Service, and state agencies for various issues of non-compliance.
One Department of Justice investigation that begun in 1994[2]was terminated in April 2007, with the Department of Justice declining prosecution.
However, another investigation on a different matter was begun by the Civil Division of the Department of Justice in June 2006 and is currently ongoing.
[3] In January 2007, the U.S. Department of Education lifted its restrictions on the company opening new schools or acquiring existing ones.[
CEC's most profitable division, American InterContinental University, has been on probation since December 2005 with its accrediting agency, SACS.[5]
The probation status was reviewed after one year, in December 2006, and extended an additional 12 months.In
December 2007, SACS is scheduled to determine whether AIU will have its probation lifted or will lose its' accreditation status.[6] [edit] External links
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="177" end="182" value="fake" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="0" end="4" value="All"/>
<opinion start="30" end="35" value="dumb" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="20">
<text>
I am an Elementary Ed student with Saint Leo University at one of the satelite campuses.
Overall my experience with the teachers has rated a 5 out of 5. The instruction has been wonderful.
The Academic Advisor has always been willing to listen and she is an exceptional administrator.
However, One particular (adjunct) instructor is very limited when it comes to using a computer and her evaluations and comments are not consistant.
She does not seem to be able to work with students who have disabilitys.
I have had great reveiws up until now and may not graduate because one observer has thrown a wrench in things.
It is scary to think that you can work hard for four years only to have one person ruin it for you.
I would reccomend anyone taking Elementary Education to think twice about taking it at a satelite campus or at least request an observer who is competent if they are uncomfortable with the person observing them.
However, The teachers are outstanding and the instruction and assessment is fair.Saint Leo truly cares about its students but will not admit or send another observer if you request one to get a second opinion.
It is not worth the expense to go into elementary education if you can lose it all at the last minute.
You would be better off getting a degree in another feild and then applying for certification with the Department of Education.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="196" end="213" value="Academic Advisor"/>
<opinion start="261" end="273" value="exceptional" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="101" end="112" value="experience"/>
<opinion start="142" end="153" value="5 out of 5" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="955" end="964" value="teachers"/>
<opinion start="968" end="980" value="outstanding" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="159" end="171" value="instruction"/>
<opinion start="180" end="190" value="wonderful" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="326" end="337" value="instructor"/>
<opinion start="345" end="353" value="limited" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="21">
<text>
I have been an online student for two trimesters now and the professors were very good.
At first they seemed a little pompus, but as the trimester continued they were much more helpfull.
I took two classes and I spent more time on reading assignments and homework than I ever did at traditional colleges.
However, I do feel that I learned the material better.
The insight coaches were also great.
The only problem I had was the fact that financial aid called every week of the trimester and still screwed my bill up.
It was easily corrected by my advisor, but it upset me greatly.
The school has a good name and from the instructors I had they deserve it...
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="159" end="164" value="they"/>
<opinion start="179" end="188" value="helpfull" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="98" end="103" value="they"/>
<opinion start="119" end="126" value="pompus" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="61" end="72" value="professors"/>
<opinion start="82" end="87" value="good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="525" end="528" value="It"/>
<opinion start="532" end="549" value="easily corrected" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="569" end="572" value="it"/>
<opinion start="572" end="578" value="upset" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="608" end="618" value="good name"/>
<opinion start="654" end="665" value="deserve it" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="445" end="459" value="financial aid"/>
<opinion start="413" end="421" value="problem" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="378" end="386" value="coaches"/>
<opinion start="396" end="402" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="22">
<text>
I'm in my second block of classes, and to be perfectly honest the classes are way way too easy.
I was enrolled at my local community college for one semester, and decided to transfer to UoP because it would be more convenient.
Staff I would rate a 3/5, they are courteous, but can take a long time to respond.
Grading I rate a 0/5, they grade much too easily, I have never been good at english, I'm a math/science person, I have failed english and writing courses several times, and I got a 96% at the end of the semester.
The grading is TOO LENIENT!
I don't know about transfering the credits out, but I am going to check into it soon at the community college, sacrificing a good education for convenience is just not worth it for me.

But for all those out there that wish to have a degree that is worth less than a real degree, &quot;to each his own&quot;
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="231" end="237" value="Staff"/>
<opinion start="267" end="277" value="courteous" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="67" end="75" value="classes"/>
<opinion start="87" end="96" value="too easy" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="23">
<text>
This supposedly military friendly school scammed me.
CTU was extremely helpful at first and I enjoyed the classes while at the same time was challenged by them.
One complaint I have is that I was put into a program where I was not allowed to choose my classes.
It may have changed but there was a preset list of classes I had to take despite already having credit in some of them.
I had multiple units in Computer Science and Networking as I had been doing it in the military for 6 years at the time.
CTU was still trying to get me to take 101.

After about 2 semesters, I was deployed to an area without internet access because of military duties.
Since classes already started, CTU told me they would extend me so that I could complete the classes and get credit once I got back.
What they failed to tell me is in order to extend, I also had to be enrolled in the next semester.
By the time I got back from my deployment, I had racked up 2 full time semesters worth of fees and no credits to show for it.
I called the school to explain the situation I was in and thought it was taken care of.
When I enrolled in another school, they even released my transcripts which isn't supposed to happen if you owe them money.
Next thing I know, there's a letter in the mail from a collection agency saying I still owe CTU the money.
This is 3 years later.
They NEVER contacted me in that whole 3 year period.

If you can complete the program without problems or having to take any breaks, go for it.
Just be sure to read between the lines in dealing with any school belonging to Career Education Corporation.
There are several under federal investigation.

Read this: http://www.cbsnews.com/stories/2005/01/31/60minutes/main670479.shtml

If you are a veteran, go to American Military University (AMU).
In my personal opinion, the experience with AMU has been much more satisfying.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="34" end="41" value="school"/>
<opinion start="41" end="52" value="scammed me" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="209" end="217" value="program"/>
<opinion start="167" end="177" value="complaint" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="34" end="41" value="school"/>
<opinion start="16" end="34" value="military friendly" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="54" end="58" value="CTU"/>
<opinion start="72" end="80" value="helpful" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="107" end="115" value="classes"/>
<opinion start="95" end="103" value="enjoyed" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="107" end="115" value="classes"/>
<opinion start="142" end="153" value="challenged" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="24">
<text>
I am looking at many online universities, and JIU seems to have the best Ed.D program in leadership.
The admissions office has been helpful.
It may be more expensive, but I think my degree will be earned and not bought.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="74" end="87" value="Ed.D program"/>
<opinion start="69" end="74" value="best" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="144" end="147" value="It"/>
<opinion start="159" end="169" value="expensive" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="107" end="125" value="admissions office"/>
<opinion start="134" end="142" value="helpful" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="25">
<text>
I have not experienced any major problems with UMUC.
Most of the course I have taken were well structured and facilitated learning.
You do have to rely upon yourself to learn the material, but the weekly assignments complemented the assigned reading.
In order to succeed at UMUC you have to be self motivated and well disciplined.
I wonder how many of the people posting negative ratings here have obtained a degree at all.
I have completed 96 hours with UMUC and have had a positive experience for the most part.
Granted it is not a perfect systems and some instructors are more involved than others, but it has and will help me in my career.
As for the the person who doesn't list their Master's degree recieved from UMUC on their resume you must have some educational pedigree.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="529" end="532" value="it"/>
<opinion start="541" end="549" value="perfect" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="47" end="52" value="UMUC"/>
<opinion start="33" end="42" value="problems" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="490" end="501" value="experience"/>
<opinion start="481" end="490" value="positive" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="361" end="368" value="people"/>
<topic start="385" end="393" value="ratings"/>
<opinion start="376" end="385" value="negative" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="66" end="73" value="course"/>
<opinion start="111" end="132" value="facilitated learning" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="66" end="73" value="course"/>
<opinion start="91" end="107" value="well structured" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="207" end="219" value="assignments"/>
<opinion start="219" end="232" value="complemented" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="26">
<text>
UOP provides you all the tools to obtain your degree.
Yes, there are some people in the classes that do not belong there.
Yes, there are some instructors that appear unqualified to teach at a college-level.
The school is not perfect.
Who knew?


Personally, I have been relatively pleased with my experience at UOP.
I have found it to be more difficult than attending traditional classes.
They really load you down with work to justify giving you credit hours.
Also, learning is easier for me in a physical classroom environment.
I like the face-to-face interaction with the class and instructor.
However, I have made the experience work for me.


The people that have degraded the degree have their reasons I suppose.
Prior to attending the college, I made phone calls to businesses to ask for opinions of online degrees.
The fact that I will have an online degree does not disqualify me from an interview.
My work experience, how I interview, and my desire to succeed is what hiring managers care about.
In todays world, those are the things that are important.
Weaknesses in one of those areas can easily be overlooked because of the strengths in the other two.


The college is what you make of it.
People can complain about their experiences if they want.
Other people can say UOP is the best school for anyone wanting a degree to attend.
The fact of the mater is this, you can achieve the same goal by taking other avenues.
Most companies will not be impressed by an UOP degree.
Most companies will not be unimpressed by an UOP degree.
The important thing is that you get an education.
How you use that education and succeed in life depends on you.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="397" end="402" value="They"/>
<opinion start="409" end="423" value="load you down" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="216" end="223" value="school"/>
<opinion start="230" end="238" value="perfect" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="317" end="321" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="251" end="262" value="Personally" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="586" end="592" value="class"/>
<opinion start="543" end="548" value="like" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="317" end="321" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="287" end="295" value="pleased" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1191" end="1199" value="college"/>
<opinion start="1202" end="1216" value="what you make" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="336" end="339" value="it"/>
<opinion start="350" end="360" value="difficult" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="146" end="158" value="instructors"/>
<opinion start="170" end="182" value="unqualified" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="1455" end="1460" value="Most"/>
<topic start="1498" end="1502" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="1482" end="1492" value="impressed" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="76" end="83" value="people"/>
<opinion start="110" end="117" value="belong" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="1511" end="1516" value="Most"/>
<topic start="1556" end="1560" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="1538" end="1550" value="unimpressed" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="0" end="4" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="17" end="21" value="all" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="1283" end="1296" value="Other people"/>
<topic start="1304" end="1308" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="1315" end="1320" value="best" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="27">
<text>
I've heard horror stories from DeVry alums who had received financial aid that even once the balance was paid, they kept adding charges and sending statements demanding more money.
Has anyone here had that experience?
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="37" end="43" value="alums"/>
<topic start="31" end="37" value="DeVry"/>
<opinion start="11" end="26" value="horror stories" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="28">
<text>
As a CTU grad, I can say that CTU is on par with any traditional school in the country.
The business administration degree I earned helped me land a position as a pharmaceutical sales rep.
100k/year.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="31" end="35" value="CTU"/>
<opinion start="38" end="45" value="on par" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="29">
<text>
All you have submitted are accusations that have not went forth to determine CTU as an unfit educational institution.
Walmart and Home Depot have accusations applied to them almost on a daily basis.
We can't stop venture capitalist or investment firms from purchasing what they think is an investment.
This is why we have checks and balances including government oversight.
Anyone can accuse someone for something....
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="4" end="8" value="you"/>
<topic start="77" end="81" value="CTU"/>
<opinion start="67" end="77" value="determine" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="30">
<text>
I am currently going to DeVry.
I went to a state college like some of the posters said is better this was in FL.
I left the school 1 semester away from my Associate's degree because the education was so horrible.
I already knew most of the stuff before the classes began, most classes I did not even have to open the book and I got an A. I left there with a 3.90 GPA.
Besides some pain in the butt financial aid issues that were resolved my education at DeVry has been great.
I was really worried about going there because of how much bashing the school takes.
The classes I have taken are actually challenging, the teachers know a lot more than the teachers at my previous college.
I know someone posted something about throwing out applications that have a school where you only go 2 years for a Bachelors degree.
I'm not sure where this person was so seriously misinformed, but going full time it takes 3 1/2 years, so that is a whole 6 months less than a traditional college.
We do have 8 week terms instead of 12 weeks, but that does not mean that we do less work.
It is the same amount of work just a shorter time frame.
I learn more in an 8 week class at DeVry than probably my whole wasted education at my previous college.
Are they the greatest college out there?
Of course not.
But they do over a great education my classes have been challenging and the teachers educated.
I go online so I cannot say about any of the locations.
So do not believe that the traditional college is so much better and DeVry is a scam.
I have went to a traditional college and friends that went to them and what I have learned at DeVry is much more advanced than any of those other colleges.
Again it is not the best school, but neither are all of the traditional colleges, and the ones that are really good are also hard to get into.
I was suckered by a traditional college that did nothing to prepare me for the field I was studying; DeVry on the other hand is actually preparing me for my intended field as well as educating me on other aspects meaning there is more than one field I could go into.
It is kind of overpriced, but it's still a great education and it cost only a little more than the traditional college that I wasted almost 2 years of my life at.
I actually had a class on Macromedia Flash, yeah now Adobe where I knew more than the teacher and I taught her a whole bunch of stuff about the application and I answered all of the students classes.
So yeah traditional colleges look great on paper, just don't expect to learn too much.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1179" end="1185" value="DeVry"/>
<opinion start="1146" end="1157" value="learn more" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1953" end="1959" value="DeVry"/>
<opinion start="1989" end="2002" value="preparing me" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1953" end="1959" value="DeVry"/>
<opinion start="2035" end="2048" value="educating me" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1711" end="1714" value="it"/>
<opinion start="1725" end="1730" value="best" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1642" end="1648" value="DeVry"/>
<opinion start="1661" end="1670" value="advanced" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="573" end="581" value="classes"/>
<opinion start="607" end="619" value="challenging" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1346" end="1354" value="classes"/>
<opinion start="1364" end="1376" value="challenging" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="404" end="425" value="financial aid issues"/>
<opinion start="387" end="404" value="pain in the butt" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1333" end="1343" value="education"/>
<opinion start="1327" end="1333" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="475" end="481" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="2170" end="2180" value="education"/>
<opinion start="2164" end="2170" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="2120" end="2123" value="It"/>
<opinion start="2134" end="2145" value="overpriced" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1384" end="1393" value="teachers"/>
<opinion start="1393" end="1402" value="educated" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="31">
<text>
Went to capella for my masters in general psych and am attending now for my ph.d in the same program.
I plan to get my license (in California) to practice psychology.
I find the process challenging, the teachers good, and the courses expensive.
My only gripe about the program is that it's not APA approved, a process that takes any school a few years to accomplish.
I know personally that Capella is rapidly attempting to gain APA accreditation.
The APA approval won't affect me (most states do not require APA approval for licenser) but I'd still rather have it for credibility.
Then again, I plan to open a private practice and have blue cross send me most of my paitients.
Most pt's don't care where you went to school, so long as it's accredited and you have your license.
I seem to have the personality that really matches online courses (self-discipline, ability to manage time, basic computing skills, rather introverted).
If you're considering Capella (or any online institution) do yourself a favor and take an online course at your local community college.
If you seem to do well in that format, you'll know that online learning might be for you.
What I like about capella is that they are rapidly working to increase their prestige.
Mark my words, in a few years, haveing a masters will be as important as having a bachelors, and many people who don't want to commute or already have roots in a small town not close to a major U will opt for the online route.
At that point, Capella will become much, much more selective, which will then increase its prestige.
Might just make it the ivy of the online format.
Those interested in Capella might also want to check out Walden and Fielding.
Do not look to the U. of Pheonix or devry-- which have horrible reputations.
The site www.capellauniversitysucks.us/ is written by one disgruntled ex-student kicked out for making abusive comments during an online course.
Take the whole site with a massive grain of salt.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="232" end="240" value="courses"/>
<opinion start="240" end="250" value="expensive" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="208" end="217" value="teachers"/>
<opinion start="217" end="222" value="good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="182" end="190" value="process"/>
<opinion start="190" end="202" value="challenging" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="32">
<text>
Hi, I am considering a MA degree in I/O Psychology from Capella.
Can anybody tell me about their experiences with this program?
I would also like to hear about experiences with employer's accept of the such a degree.
</text>
</sentence>
<sentence id="33">
<text>
I am a proud full time Mother of an 11 year old son; a wife; and during the day a hard working IT Program Manager for a major automotive company.
The University of Phoenix is a blast and with only three classes left I am sad that the program is almost over.
I complete my final class on May 1st, 2006.
I have really enjoyed being able to attend an accelerated program.
I have never had the time to get board with any given topic.
While the program is challenging it has been a wonderful learning experience.
I plan to move onto a Masters program upon completing the program here.
After working in the IT field since 1984 I am happy to say that the topic of Information Technology is never a boring one.
I thank the college for their wonderful program that emphasized team work; individual study; and even included global collaboration with people from all backgrounds.
I would like to thank my professors as well for a wonderful job!
I also owe thanks to my mentor for believing in me--pressing me to move the bar further to better myself.
What started out as something for the work environment has become a personally enriching experience.
I never imagined that I would strive to maintain a GPA so that I may graduate with a degree that shows the seal of honors.
That has been my goal for quite sometime.
After a few classes, it was no longer about doing this to move a head on the job.
It is about seeing the world through new eyes based on the world known as education.
From Socrates to Plato, Critical Thinking to Java, Geography of World Commerce to eCommerce--we have learned to see things in a new light.
We have grown and this turned in to an enriching experience that none of us will ever forget.
I am truly blessed for family, friends, fellow students, and to have had the privilege of learning....Many take education for granted when there are people in the world who cannot even get their basic needs met.
You see before school here at UoP I thought global about work; however, never about the global people--there is a difference.
A huge vast world to see and learn about--we have only scratched the surface here!
I am more tuned in to the world and technology, I can proudly say.
I also care more about my neighbors around the world in a new way.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1978" end="1982" value="UoP"/>
<opinion start="2059" end="2075" value="is a difference" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="754" end="762" value="program"/>
<opinion start="744" end="754" value="wonderful" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="1145" end="1156" value="experience" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="1676" end="1686" value="enriching" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1655" end="1660" value="this"/>
<opinion start="1686" end="1697" value="experience" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="366" end="374" value="program"/>
<opinion start="322" end="330" value="enjoyed" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="1609" end="1635" value="see things in a new light" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="908" end="919" value="professors"/>
<opinion start="933" end="943" value="wonderful" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="153" end="175" value="University of Phoenix"/>
<opinion start="180" end="186" value="blast" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="448" end="456" value="program"/>
<opinion start="504" end="515" value="experience" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="34">
<text>
I came from microbiology background and I wanted a management position in life sciences so I attended university of phoenix online.
For me it was a great experience because I learned many new business concepts.
I think university of phoenix online provides excellent educational opportunity for professionals who work full-time and want to persue with a graduate program in MBA.
Overall, I was satisfied with UOP Online.
My GPA was 3.73.
Mr. Arslan
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="140" end="143" value="it"/>
<opinion start="149" end="166" value="great experience" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="221" end="250" value="university of phoenix online"/>
<opinion start="259" end="269" value="excellent" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="35">
<text>
University of Phoenix was a surprising disappointment.
As a working professional, I have two bachelors, I oversee multi-million dollar estates, and will spend 60 or 70-hours a week at work if the job demands it.
I'm not a stranger to hard work.
I enrolled and was accepted into the MBA program and was greeted by many happy, helpful people that went the extra mile to get me enrolled in the university.
Unfortunately, by my 4th class I was fully aware of a frustrating trend that my fellow classmates also commented on regularly.


The professors are more of a conversation mediator among the students than an actual professor.
Assignments were passed down, but when asked to clarify the assignment because the syllabus had contradicting, poorly worded, information, my professors regularly responded....&quot;refer to the syllabus&quot;....but wait, the syllabus IS the question.
It never seemed to matter.


The biggest issue I had with UOP is that the professors really didn't seem to care.
Students would be expected to post generally around 2 postings a day for four days (8-postings minimum, 200-words min.
per posting...and that's just to get your 2-points for attendance/participation that week); in addition there were the normal assignments to complete as well (anywhere from 200-words to 3000+ words), these could be work 7 to 20-points.
For a master's level program, I had expected and welcomed a heavy workload.
By my 2nd and 3rd class in the program, a 10-17 page paper wasn't uncommon.
The disappointing part of the program was that the professors would generally only mark your postings with a green S (substantiative=good) or a red U (unsubstantiative=poor).
You could only see the professor's marks for your posting, not for anyone else's.
If someone posted something that was off target for the class, only that person and the professor would know.
It was very easy for people in the class to spend time reading and studying a topic that had no bearing on the intended class forum.
Discussions would regularly take side steps and stray away from the topics at hand.
If you organized everyone in the class by how much they contributed to the topic and to the conversations, the professors always seemed to be towards the bottom of the list.


I found that I spent most of my time learning from my fellow students.
The &quot;real-life&quot; experience of the professors were never passed along.
A standard response from my professors would be that of a sentence fragment.
Assignments and Discussion Questions (DQs) seemed like they were copied and pasted from previous classes.
The responses to the student's postings were minimal.
By the time I transferred out of UOP, I was posting between 15 to 25 postings per week plus assignments just get meet the requirements.
In a 6-week class, I only counted 3 comments from the professors directly to me and two directed to my team.
Who's on the other end &quot;teaching&quot; these courses?


As for the program as a whole, it is organized in a semi-structured manner.
Finding your way through the site is above average and the tools provided (such as the writing center) are great!
The materials being kept online is a bit cumbersome.
Personally I like to have books I can flip through, highlight things, or be able to keep my finger on a page to flip back and forth as I dwell into a concept.
Ebooks, are less friendly in this fashion.
Plan on taking a lot of notes as your read or you'll be lost when you have to quote the text (which you will regularly do!
Every week in order to get full points!!!!)

Now when it comes to the staff, they are very close to the same level as the faculty.
My academic counselor was nearly non-existent; emails generally went unanswered or had a generic response referring to documents kept on the website.
Trying to get anyone to actually answer a question directly basically never happened (staff or faculty).


When I finally decided to transfer out of UOP, I notified three people of my intention (my academic counselor, my enrollment counselor, and my financial counselor); not one of them has ever asked me why am I leaving, is there anything they can do or check into, would a different program be better, is there something going on in my life that is causing the problem, is it the university, would I like to put my studies on hold and try again later....nothing!
The only communication I had was from my financial counselor regarding the status of my student loans.


While the University of Phoenix claims to be a University, I never found the &quot;higher education&quot; there.
Before considering enrolling in the University of Phoenix, do some web searches for online degree programs.
Don't just go with the ones at the top of the list as they are generally the schools that simply put the most money into marketing their name; as I have learned you don't always get what you pay for!
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="0" end="22" value="University of Phoenix"/>
<opinion start="39" end="54" value="disappointment" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="340" end="347" value="people"/>
<opinion start="352" end="372" value="went the extra mile" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="3085" end="3090" value="site"/>
<opinion start="3165" end="3171" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="340" end="347" value="people"/>
<opinion start="332" end="340" value="helpful" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="3177" end="3187" value="materials"/>
<opinion start="3214" end="3225" value="cumbersome" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="2398" end="2409" value="professors"/>
<opinion start="2409" end="2420" value="were never" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="959" end="970" value="professors"/>
<opinion start="992" end="997" value="care" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="4542" end="4564" value="University of Phoenix"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="4564" end="4571" value="claims" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1549" end="1557" value="program"/>
<opinion start="1523" end="1537" value="disappointing" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="544" end="555" value="professors"/>
<opinion start="559" end="615" value="more of a conversation mediator among the students than" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="3708" end="3718" value="counselor"/>
<opinion start="3729" end="3742" value="non-existent" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="783" end="794" value="professors"/>
<opinion start="750" end="764" value="poorly worded" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="3641" end="3646" value="they"/>
<opinion start="3655" end="3661" value="close" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="36">
<text>
Capella University was a complete waste of time and money.
The only rigorous experiences you can expect are their attempts to drain your pocketbook.
Having attended real universities, prior to paying a huge amount of money to Capella, I was appalled at the lack of academic integrity basically, pay your money and you'll finish.
One of the bizarre things you'll notice about Capella and their students is that they refer to themselves as &quot;learners&quot; - that should be almost offensive to anyone who is really concerned with the attainment of a genuinely rigorous educational undertaking: a cat can learn to use a litter box, a rat can learn to use a Skinner box, a dog can learn to drool when a bell has been struck.
Learning can be a passive activity that also implies there is a finite point at which it stops (which is what you'll experience at Capella).
A student, on the other hand is one who is actively engaged in the acquisition of new knowledge; a process that never stops.
If you want to be a learner who merely connects the dots of poorly written (and generic) syllabi created by faculty that really aren't actively engaged in teaching Capella is the choice for you.
Spend your money and get your piece of worthless paper.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="459" end="464" value="that"/>
<opinion start="481" end="491" value="offensive" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1246" end="1252" value="paper"/>
<opinion start="1236" end="1246" value="worthless" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1090" end="1098" value="syllabi"/>
<opinion start="1080" end="1088" value="generic" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="229" end="237" value="Capella"/>
<opinion start="245" end="254" value="appalled" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="0" end="19" value="Capella University"/>
<opinion start="34" end="58" value="waste of time and money" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1090" end="1098" value="syllabi"/>
<opinion start="1059" end="1074" value="poorly written" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="399" end="408" value="students"/>
<opinion start="346" end="354" value="bizarre" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="37">
<text>
For the sake of time - I will not comment on quality of education - let's assume it is OK compared to it's competitors.
The adminstration of the school needs to get fired.
The programs change frequently and these changes are not understood by the staff of the school leaving the learner to pay tuition while these items get sorted out.
The school has no interest in customer satisfaction and does a superior job of recrutiment - but makes no committment to it's current learners who are often left to sort out the schools issues and pay ridiculous amounts of tuition.
The school never admits fault - desipte its frequent unorganization.
Considering it has a business school - it is one of the most poorly run business I have ever been associated with.
I would not recommend Capella to ANYONE.
There are better institutions out there.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="562" end="570" value="tuition"/>
<opinion start="540" end="551" value="ridiculous" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="418" end="430" value="recrutiment"/>
<opinion start="402" end="411" value="superior" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="125" end="139" value="adminstration"/>
<opinion start="153" end="172" value="needs to get fired" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="681" end="684" value="it"/>
<opinion start="703" end="714" value="poorly run" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="45" end="66" value="quality of education"/>
<opinion start="87" end="90" value="OK" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="576" end="583" value="school"/>
<opinion start="625" end="640" value="unorganization" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="780" end="788" value="Capella"/>
<opinion start="770" end="780" value="recommend" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="38">
<text>
Instructors are serious about helping with questions.
There is a lot of dialogue among the students and among the instructors and at least two live sessions per week with instructors.
Great follow up on finding employment opportunities.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="0" end="12" value="Instructors"/>
<opinion start="16" end="24" value="serious" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="192" end="202" value="follow up"/>
<opinion start="186" end="192" value="Great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="39">
<text>
I have not been, nor will I ever be, a student at capella, but what everyone on this forum seems to be forgetting, or at least ignorant of, is the fact that the APA will not accredit capella so all of you out there who are getting the PhD in Psych, beware.
</text>
</sentence>
<sentence id="40">
<text>
The University of Phoenix doesn't get enough credit.
Its on-line program, the first in the world,has proven this is a viable route for many people to earn a higher education, in fact most colleges are scrambling to follow its lead.
The Uninversity has a group of highly educated Facilitators and the 24/7 tech support team is first rate with easy access.
I would highly recommend this school.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="309" end="327" value="tech support team"/>
<opinion start="330" end="341" value="first rate" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="4" end="26" value="University of Phoenix"/>
<opinion start="34" end="52" value="get enough credit" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="390" end="397" value="school"/>
<opinion start="375" end="385" value="recommend" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="41">
<text>
Capellastudent,On one side, I think you are correct in saying that it is clear that the fellow who runs the anti capella websites also is posting here.
However, he is not the only person who has expressed concerns about their degrees, and I can guarantee you that, at least in my case, I have not posted anywhere else on the subject.Regarding the argument you make about teaching, it has several problems.
First, just because 80% of these people are teaching, does not mean that the capella degree got them those jobs, or that the degree will be considered by those institutions when they have completed it.
I know someone who was hired as professionally qualified with a master's degree.
They are enrolled in an online program for a Ph.D. but their institution has already indicated that they will not recognize the degree, nor allow the person to use the title Dr. when they have it.Second, you do not specify the type of employment (adjunct, full-time, tenure track ect.).
I know quite a few people with Master's degrees who teach as adjuncts.
I also know several who teach full-time, but in non-tenure-track positions.Third,
you don't mention what type of schools they are teaching at.
The vast majority of people with unaccredited (professionally) Ph.D.s tend to work at private colleges or community colleges.
If that's your goal, then you're fine.
I will reiterate however, that most colleges of business will not consider a Ph.D. from a non-AACSB college of business.
I suspect it is similar in other fields that have professional accrediting bodies.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="164" end="167" value="he"/>
<topic start="229" end="237" value="degrees"/>
<opinion start="198" end="208" value="expressed" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="37" end="41" value="you"/>
<opinion start="31" end="37" value="think" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="501" end="508" value="degree"/>
<opinion start="479" end="484" value="mean" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="42">
<text>
I just started taking courses toward an MBA Degree at UoP, and I have to say I'm already disappointed.
I made the mistake of upsetting one of my, supposedly professional, professors and he took it upon himself to find reasons to second guess every decision I made.

I know myself, and I know my weaknesses.
I don't shy away from an opportunity to work on my weaknesses, but it's hard when you try, and the best constructive criticism you can get is &quot;I don't like the way this is written.
Redo it and get it to me by 11:59.&quot;

That's not teaching, it's micro managing and helping others to develop a habit of regurgitation.
Anyone can feed you things to say in the form of &quot;here's what I want you to say, and here's how you should say it&quot;, but that's not the reality of a leading professional.
You will never get ahead by planning to say one step behind.

I've made the decision to attend another institution, and I recommend you do the same before you waste your hard earned money.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="54" end="58" value="UoP"/>
<opinion start="90" end="103" value="disappointed" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="547" end="556" value="teaching"/>
<opinion start="563" end="578" value="micro managing" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="43">
<text>
My experience at DeVry is by far one of the worst I've had.
I went to the financial aids many time requesting information about my loans and scholarship and where my money is going to but the faculty there never wants to give me the information that should belong to me.
From experience, if you pester a professor enough, you'll pass..even if you're the dumbest person around.. you just need to talk your way to a good grade.
DeVry's employee are lazy and incompetent.
The career advisors seemed to always be walking around and not doing what they're being paid to do.
No one is ever at the cashier office.. there's always a note saying 'For Cashier, go to Student Finance'.. and when you go there, no one is there to help you either.
The professors talk more about themselves then they do the subject they're supposed to teach.
If you're a girl, you basically just have to wait 3 yrs for your degree.
Every class seems to always be a review of the first day of class that semester, which is basically the syllabus and introduction.
Out of all the professor, I'd say two actually cared about the students' well-being.. and yes, they left the school already because they knew what a fraud the school has become.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="441" end="450" value="employee"/>
<opinion start="454" end="459" value="lazy" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="3" end="14" value="experience"/>
<opinion start="44" end="50" value="worst" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1217" end="1224" value="school"/>
<opinion start="1207" end="1213" value="fraud" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="441" end="450" value="employee"/>
<opinion start="463" end="475" value="incompetent" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="44">
<text>
This online university is just that.
It fits my schedule, I don't have to be logged in at any particular time and I get EXCELLENT customer sevice.
The professors e-mail you, the school checks in to be sure you're ok with the next set of courses.
AND they share their experiences about the classes they've had and what you might be going into.
This is what an online univerisity experience is all about.
To put the icing on the cake they are regionally accredited!
Job Well Done, Jones!
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="38" end="41" value="It"/>
<opinion start="41" end="58" value="fits my schedule" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="488" end="494" value="Jones"/>
<opinion start="476" end="486" value="Well Done" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="132" end="148" value="customer sevice"/>
<opinion start="122" end="132" value="EXCELLENT" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="45">
<text>
I recently graduated from the UOP Pasadena, CA campus and was accepted to the Loyola Marymount MBA/MS Systems Engineering program.
If you can look past the study groups and manage the costs (I am a veteran and receive the other 50% from my employer), it's a pretty good school.
I can imagine why many become disenchanted over the cost though.
Course workload is daunting, but you can't beat the flexibility.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="302" end="307" value="many"/>
<topic start="336" end="341" value="cost"/>
<opinion start="314" end="327" value="disenchanted" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="350" end="366" value="Course workload"/>
<opinion start="369" end="378" value="daunting" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="46">
<text>
Man for everyone satisfied you will find 10 POed about something.
I attend CTU and frankly I prefer it over brick and mortar BS.
In a B and M you have the class clowns, the ones that are there for social status and then those who ride the backs of others.
I have been there for some time and yes there is good and bad.
Where isn't there after all?
I admit that when we get people that constantly say I'm confused I believe they belong in a B and M.
Another thing and I am sorry to say this.
I honestly wonder why some of the people are there even.
I mean seriously it is Unversity level grammar and professional based workmanship, not HS.
The thing about CTU that people do not understand is that their course are degree specfic.
Not a meld with emphassis on a subject.
It is true it is hard and challenging.
The instructors are there to help, but they will not give answers.
It is our job to figure and show we grasp the meaning of what we are supposed to be learning.
Can you do that on a paper with a multiple choice quiz?
It is high impact and self paced learning, with that do not fall behind.
We utilize research tactics that we are left to explore and believe it or not the teachers learn from us.
They are true professionals in the field that they are teaching, not a tenderd professional student.
I did look into other schools and I choose CTU for my reasons, not because of someone elses thoughts.
If that was the case I would not buy dog food at Wal Mart.
An education is something that is earned from various walks of life.
Where you recieve that education is your choice.
I am not championing CTU, it is only one of many options.
If you can not work on your and commit do not attend an online campus.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1044" end="1047" value="It"/>
<opinion start="1050" end="1062" value="high impact" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="794" end="797" value="it"/>
<opinion start="800" end="805" value="hard" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="794" end="797" value="it"/>
<opinion start="809" end="821" value="challenging" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="47">
<text>
I am on my 8th course at Capella and have had very good interaction with my instructors as well as my fellow learners.
Those that say this is a Diploma mill need to take a better look.
It is accredited by the same body that accredits the University of Illinois and other Big 10 schools.
That means that a diploma from Capella is worth the same as a diploma from the University of Illinois.
It is by no means a diploma mill.
The course work is challenging and I do not feel like I am being short changed.
Also, the cost of the university is inline with all of the other private colleges and universities throughout the United States.
Full time tuition is roughly $12,000 a year.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="120" end="126" value="Those"/>
<topic start="135" end="140" value="this"/>
<opinion start="145" end="158" value="Diploma mill" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="56" end="68" value="interaction"/>
<opinion start="51" end="56" value="good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="394" end="397" value="It"/>
<opinion start="414" end="427" value="diploma mill" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="494" end="508" value="short changed" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="433" end="445" value="course work"/>
<opinion start="448" end="460" value="challenging" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="48">
<text>
I have recently enrolled in UOP online/flexnet.
The experience is a joke.
I am pursuing an accounting degree and have attended community college for two years.
THe first class is a breeze just to get you used to the format of the class.
I checked on my next 3 classes and there was absolutely nothing relevant to accounting besides the importance and history.
The textbooks I read through reminded me of a history or english class.
Anybody who takes the time to do the work will get an A. Grades should be determined by attendance, effort, and skills learned.
Not attendance and effort.
Learning to write essays on the importance of accounting is ridiculous, and I believe that a person who hopes to gain knowledge of accounting and be able to have a career in the accounting field should steer clear of UOP.
UOP disgraces academics by collecting tuition from students and giving useless information for working adults which will only teach the adults how to write reports.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="816" end="820" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="677" end="807" value="believe that a person who hopes to gain knowledge of accounting and be able to have a career in the accounting field should steer" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="264" end="272" value="classes"/>
<opinion start="305" end="314" value="relevant" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="822" end="826" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="826" end="836" value="disgraces" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="53" end="64" value="experience"/>
<opinion start="69" end="74" value="joke" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="49">
<text>
In general I have been pleased with UOP instruction and technical support is excellent, but their response times with the newsgroups are often unacceptable.
UOP needs to put some more money into infrastructure even if it has to take some away from their huge advertising budget.
Slow response times or no connectivity at all are becoming much too frequent as they push for more students without sufficiently upgrading infrastructure.
I'm not sure I can continue recommending UOP to other students unless they correct these issues.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="36" end="40" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="23" end="31" value="pleased" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="479" end="483" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="466" end="479" value="recommending" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="362" end="367" value="they"/>
<opinion start="367" end="372" value="push" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="159" end="163" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="163" end="169" value="needs" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="50">
<text>
You're lying my friend got an &quot;A&quot; on the knowledge check test and missed none.
She showed me her knowledge check test and I saw it with my own eyes.
So, you should want to consider telling the truth next time?
Just because you can't pass the knowledge check tests doesn't give you the right to lie about people not making above a D+. Pay attention to your classes and actually read the e-books.
</text>
</sentence>
<sentence id="51">
<text>
The university does a fine job of providing distance graduate education.
Some argue it to be a diploma mill without understanding the facts of the school.
Its fully accreditited by the Higher Learning Commission, the same regional accreditation body that certifies the Air Force Academy, the University of Chicago, Indiana University, Kent State, Purdue and a host of others.
It suffered some growing pains as any organization with its growth rate would, and perhaps it didn't manage its quality with as much perfection as one would have hoped; but its nothing like the University of Phoenix in terms of being oversized or targeting a lowest common denominator.
Those who can't write well or conduct proper research fail to finish the program.
They can't pass their comps, and they can't complete their dissertations.
Anyone who wants evidence of the quality of a Capella graduate can either stand by for the stories of their success to come, or read the published research completed by these students available at http://wwwlib.umi.com/dissertations/search/advanced/school and enter Capella.
Its a fine school, with over 70% of the faculty terminally degreed, and it gives the chance for bright, hard working, non-traditional students to prove themselves from anywhere in the world.
There are soldiers in Iraq working nights on their degrees at Capella.
Nothing wrong with that.
Those with sour grapes couldnt cut it, have an ax to grind, and are devoting their time to smearing the school.
Naturally, if you want to devote your time and talent to a traditional graduate degree program then go for it.
Its a noble undertaking.
Its a proven honor.
If youre a working professional or at a point in your life where you cant sacrifice the time to return to a brick and mortar environment for several years but still think you have what it takes to contribute to academia and earn your credentials, right now Capella is probably the best choice you have.
On-line education is here to stay.
Its the 21st century after all.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="1403" end="1426" value="Those with sour grapes"/>
<topic start="1509" end="1516" value="school"/>
<opinion start="1496" end="1505" value="smearing" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="559" end="563" value="its"/>
<opinion start="620" end="630" value="oversized" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1247" end="1256" value="students"/>
<opinion start="1216" end="1229" value="hard working" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1247" end="1256" value="students"/>
<opinion start="1207" end="1214" value="bright" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1109" end="1113" value="Its"/>
<opinion start="1115" end="1120" value="fine" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="74" end="79" value="Some"/>
<topic start="85" end="88" value="it"/>
<opinion start="96" end="109" value="diploma mill" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="62" end="72" value="education"/>
<opinion start="22" end="31" value="fine job" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="52">
<text>
I graduated from AIU online with a BIT Programming.
I decided to finish my education with a online school after 8 years of attending a State Uni.
I had a serious problem with the state uni, I was never able to get into any of my classes, due to time constraints, I worked fulltime all the way through school, and because freshman had priority on all GE classes.
What this equaled was 8 years of college, all GEs except math complete and my major classes were never scheduled so I could attend.
I ended up taking 2 classes a semester because I due to the state colleges bureaucracy I was never able to find or enroll in classes that would work with a fulltime schedule.
My biggest fear was that if I ever finished school I would never even use my degree, after all, at the time I was working in a retail store with several college grads doing the same thing as me.


I entered AIU with a beginners level in computers.
I had worked with some programming but not much.
The classes were laid out in a progressive manner, as with math you need to have a foundation before you can start building on it and AIU took this into account.
My instructors were well versed in the subjects they taught and had just as many if not more office hours than, my State Uni, that they could be approached for help.
Because it is an accelerated program the classes move fast and it is very easy to fall behind.
If you are considering AIU you will need to be ready to apply yourself in order to get the work done, because no room for procrastinators here!


The course work was very challenging and I really walked away from this school with an education I can apply to my everyday life.
I am even working a job now where I use skills that are directly related to my degree and lessons I learned at AIU.
How many other people can say that as well?
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1146" end="1158" value="instructors"/>
<opinion start="1163" end="1175" value="well versed" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1558" end="1570" value="course work"/>
<opinion start="1579" end="1591" value="challenging" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1353" end="1361" value="classes"/>
<opinion start="1386" end="1406" value="easy to fall behind" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1353" end="1361" value="classes"/>
<opinion start="1366" end="1371" value="fast" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="983" end="991" value="classes"/>
<opinion start="1010" end="1022" value="progressive" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="53">
<text>
This College was paid $2 million dollars by Household International, a predatory lender, to add a website that encourages debt among service members, and seems to disregard the Soldiers and Sailors Act which provides temporary relief to active duty service members.
Household's parent HSBC is linked to a bank owned by the former-regime of Saddam Hussein.
The bank relationship is being investigated for money laundering.
UMUC seems to have disregarded this information, took the $2 million, and turned the other way.
It is unconscionable that UMUC is supposed to provide higher education to military personnel and, at the same time, is in partnership with a predatory lender that often mishandles payments, records, and disregards the law.
UMUC should be blacklisted from US installations and banned from taxayer contracts handed out by the Department of Defense and the US Army, until it ceases its relationship with Household International.
It looks again like UMUC will do anything for money, even profiteering off soldiers serving in Iraq and Afghanistan.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="433" end="459" value="seems to have disregarded" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="5" end="13" value="College"/>
<opinion start="157" end="176" value="seems to disregard" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="553" end="558" value="UMUC"/>
<opinion start="533" end="548" value="unconscionable" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="980" end="985" value="UMUC"/>
<opinion start="963" end="980" value="looks again like" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="755" end="760" value="UMUC"/>
<opinion start="760" end="767" value="should" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="54">
<text>
I'm a senior in high school planning to attend devry university in ivring tx. and im confused on a couple of things concerning the quality of a devry degree and the education provided by the institution.

I recently heard about this forum and all of its negative comments.
I was told by a college advisor at my school, but I'm not to confident on his word.
Despite all those bad comments on the unversity, I have read a couple of good ones explaining most of those negative comments and essentially making the writers of the negative opinions sound like lazy people.
I'm hoping I could recieve some help from some of you on making my decision.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="234" end="240" value="forum"/>
<topic start="399" end="409" value="unversity"/>
<opinion start="255" end="264" value="negative" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="55">
<text>
I got my MS in CIS from UOP, and since then I have been promoted, and I am able to teach part time at a local college in my area.
Overall, my income, which was pretty good before, has risen over 20% as a DIRECT result of my degree from UOP.
I graduated from the University of Virginia (UVA) for my undergraduate degree, and the work at UOP was at least as hard as the work at UVA, which is one of the very top public schools in the nation.
I am a good writer, and UOP improved my writing.
I am a good manager, and UOP improved my management skills.
I am a good technician, and UOP improved my understanding of the interaction of business and technical aspects of our field.
UOP helped me be more disciplined in my work ethic, and UOP helped me refine my ability to communicate.
When we finished our degree program, I missed the daily debates, discussion and feedback.
The traditional model of school - lecture, reading, etc, with possibly a discussion section once per week - is not nearly as much fun as daily online interaction with a group of highly motivated, dynamic classmates.
UOP is NOT perfect - we had a couple professors that were not great (most of our professors were very good, with relevant, current field experience), and my financial aid counselors DID change constantly.
Some of our team projects were hindered by people not doing their share.
The experience would be better if they had a bit more standards as to whom they let in - we had one teammate who did not write English well, which meant we had to do or re-do most of his work on our team projects (welcome to real life!).
However, no one lied to me, pressured me, or refused to return my calls.
Actually, I almost never HAD to call anyone.
Everything was taken care of when needed.
Not a problem.
Most of my classmates stayed together through the entire program, and they were great.
The best part of the program was learning from my classmates and professors through online discussion.
Very rich experiences from which to draw.
Some people talk about accreditation: UOP is accredited the same as traditional schools - by the regional accrediting agency nationally recognized by the Dept of Education (North Central Association, in this case).
There is no higher accreditation you can get, in general.
I cannot speak about the MBA program, and what accreditation is needed for that specifically.
If the UOP MBA is not going to be recognized as much as you would like, then don't get one there.
You can find an MBA program on any street corner.
I can easily recommend UOP to a lot of people.
Not perfect, but was great for me.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="2026" end="2038" value="experiences"/>
<opinion start="2021" end="2026" value="rich" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="346" end="350" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="354" end="371" value="at least as hard" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="2638" end="2646" value="perfect" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1112" end="1116" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="1123" end="1131" value="perfect" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="2656" end="2662" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1894" end="1899" value="they"/>
<opinion start="1904" end="1910" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1933" end="1941" value="program"/>
<opinion start="1916" end="1926" value="best part" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="56">
<text>
I am a student in Axia College of University of Phoenix, and about to enter my second block of classes.
I must say that I was very skeptical of this school.
However, when it all came down to what I could do, UOP was it.
I work full time and take care of a child.
So, anything with a set schedule was out for me.
I spent months researching different online schools (I'm glad I did because I almost called ITT Tech!).
I used student reviews to make my decision, as students are the most qualified to judge.
When browsing reviews, please take time to pay attention to the grammar and spelling of those writing them.
This can give you great incite into how qualified they were to enter college to begin with.
Those who say that the grading is too lenient are right, but you must consider other factors.
Depending on your major, getting an easy &quot;A&quot; in English isn't cheating you out of anything.
In other classes, such as those that deal with specific subjects not studied in K-12, you must study to get a good grade.
There is no easy &quot;A&quot; when dealing with a subject that is not used in your everyday life.
You must also be self motivated and willing to work.
Your teachers will not call you and email you every five minutes when an assignment is due.
Since classes at Axia are not like traditional class rooms, you must be willing to learn on your own.
While there are class discussions, the only way to really get anything out of it is to spend time by yourself and learn.
One last thing I would like to add is that I have never read a review from an UOP graduate that had trouble finding a job because of where they got there degree.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1462" end="1465" value="it"/>
<opinion start="1419" end="1432" value="the only way" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="146" end="158" value="this school"/>
<opinion start="133" end="143" value="skeptical" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="57">
<text>
These reviews would be very helpful if I could determine which positive ones are school employees or not.
I just want to know if there is anyone here that has graduated from the school and can offer me any satisfaction that they have obtained after graduation.
</text>
</sentence>
<sentence id="58">
<text>
What a waste of money!
The field reps (some-most) are rude and don't want to do their jobs.
Even for DE you still have to go stand in line for an hour or so to register for your classes.
Isn't this DE, DISTANCE education?
I've taken 4 proctored exams. 1 of them was never sent and 1 was missing an entire page when received by the instructor.
Often you have no idea what your final grade is for a course because of these pitfalls until well into the next semester.
That can be rather depressing.
Don't even bother emailing the administration.
They won't respond.
UMUC brags how they cut breaks financially for military.
Their tuition is as high if not higher than that of a resident state universities.
Go to a real DE University, I am as soon as I find one that I like.
UMUC should be ashamed of themselves for even calling themselves a university.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="7" end="22" value="waste of money" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="28" end="39" value="field reps"/>
<opinion start="57" end="62" value="rude" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="538" end="553" value="administration"/>
<opinion start="507" end="525" value="Don't even bother" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="475" end="480" value="That"/>
<opinion start="494" end="505" value="depressing" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="576" end="581" value="UMUC"/>
<opinion start="581" end="587" value="brags" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="788" end="793" value="UMUC"/>
<opinion start="793" end="811" value="should be ashamed" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="59">
<text>
I have been attending UOP for nearly two years, things apparently came to an end because the inability to handle issues in a timely manner.
My financial counselor and her manager dropped the ball, when I called to speak with another manager or director they put me on hold for 25 minutes which was convenient for them because at that point it was after 5:00 pm MT.
My financial counselor is a liar and her manager is a coward.
Over time I have been experiencing issues with many of the faculty, their feedback (individual) came during the last week of class, they were unresponsive or they didnt know the material.
I honestly have to say that UOP is in it for the money rather than the success of their students.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="372" end="392" value="financial counselor"/>
<opinion start="397" end="402" value="liar" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="653" end="657" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="660" end="680" value="in it for the money" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="568" end="573" value="they"/>
<opinion start="578" end="591" value="unresponsive" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="145" end="181" value="manager  financial counselor"/>
<opinion start="181" end="198" value="dropped the ball" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="491" end="499" value="faculty"/>
<opinion start="467" end="474" value="issues" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="410" end="418" value="manager"/>
<opinion start="423" end="430" value="coward" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="22" end="26" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="94" end="104" value="inability" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="60">
<text>
Let Me Admit first off: Devry U Should adopt a stricter Admittance policy.


With A GOOD GPA you will be in demand.


Dont fool yourself: ALL UNIVERSITIES ARE FOR PROFIT (WITHOUT QUESTION)


I am currently attending Devry University and I am having a great time.
I am totally committed to this UNIVERSITY and my studies.
The classes are great, with a relatively small number of students per class.
The Professors make me feel like I am family or a good friend.
I attended Monmouth University (Very Good School) for a degree in EE many years ago before they dumped the program for Software Engineering (EE was not making money for them).
I can confess that the difference is like Night and Day.
At Devry I get Lots of Labs to reinforce the theory; at Monmouth University I get lots of theory but few labs (I need Labs, I am not good with theory only; I need to see the pictures, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN).
At Devry University the Professors go out of there way to make you understand the material giving you extra time to absorbed the concepts (Naturally you have to show interest and willingness to learn).
Here is an Example:

At Monmouth University

I had 2 semesters in Digital Electronics and One semester in Microcontrollers w/ Assembler language (Solid) with 1 senior project for a Microcontroller Car)

At DeVry University

I Get 2 Solid Semesters of Digital (Learned Twice As much including CPLDs and FPGAs (mastery)) another 2 Solid Semester of Microcontrollers (Assembler and C/C++).


AND 4 PROJECTS ALONG THE WAY

All this in the first 2 Years alone!!!!!!!!!

With More Microprocessors to come in the 2nd half of a Bachelors

This is exactly what I am looking for and maybe you are too.



ALL UNIVERSITIES ARE FOR PROFIT (WITHOUT QUESTION)
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="327" end="335" value="classes"/>
<opinion start="339" end="345" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="216" end="233" value="Devry University"/>
<opinion start="251" end="262" value="great time" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1666" end="1671" value="This"/>
<opinion start="1682" end="1704" value="what I am looking for" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="371" end="390" value="number of students"/>
<opinion start="354" end="371" value="relatively small" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="61">
<text>
The managing director of UMUC Europe is reported to publish student's names, social security account numbers, and addresses on the World Wide Web.
Someone wants to steal an identity and that person's wallet too, they need only go online to UMUC sites.
So, enroll at UMUC and have your personal identification information published ONLINE at umuc.blogspot.com
or in one of the student groups, or see thecomplaintstation.com for more details.
</text>
</sentence>
<sentence id="62">
<text>
I am the President and CEO of a large firm in New York.
The required skills of my employees, and of the rest of the emerging workforce, are almost always seen by in a University of Phoenix graduate.
I will not simply promote someone who has a degree, but I will weigh the Phoenix graduate more heavily; my experience in dealing with them permits me to make such generalizations.
From past experience, they demonstrate the ability to work with technology and have excellent communication skills.
Being forced to use the computer, be independent, and work with fellow students each day, is the closest &quot;real-world&quot; approach to Education I have seen in my thirty years in Business.


It always peaks my curiosity when I read comments about the University of Phoenix Online being too easy.
Has it ever occurred to you that you already possess those very skills that I just mentioned?
Or, on the other hand, do you even hold a degree?


Since other individuals have found it necessary to comment on whether or not UoP offers a quality education, I'm hoping that at least someone is interested to hear from a qualified individual.
I will say simply this much, I encourage continuing education and offer tuition reimbursement of up to 15 credits per year; University of Phoenix online and Walden are the only two programs I will offer this reimbursement to my over one thousand employees.
I take this all rather personally because many graduates successfuly run sectors of my company; frankly, many of you are simply clueless.
It's funny and irritating all at the same time.
Yet, I truly don't care, since you won't be on my payroll.


As an end note, I went to a community college for my undergrad and obtained my MBA from New York University.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="639" end="649" value="Education"/>
<opinion start="614" end="625" value="real-world" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="63">
<text>
I'm near completing my Bachelor's degree and I've done it online.
I will be graduating soon, but that's part of the story.
I can't say enough for the education progam and the support received.
The courses are not easy, however, they are not difficult either.


I like the idea of how the online schedule works around your schedule, and not the other way around.
I can miss a day or two and still catch up.
The hours are 24-7, therefore, I can enter a leave whenever I wish.
There are mandatory meetings, however, very few.


I've rated the professors and staff in the high 90%.
They usually respond quickly, and are well informed.
Now, there are minor times when something does not go right, but nothing is 100%

The school material can either be purchased or extracted from the services.


Personally, I think this school offers one of the most unique programs systems available, and one that anyone with a little determination can do.


As mentioned before, I'll be graduating soon, and have decided to continue into their graduate program at Keller.
If all goes well, I'll have my Master's in less than one year.


To sum my experience with DeVrt, &quot;SUPER.&quot;
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1147" end="1169" value="DeVrt experience"/>
<opinion start="1173" end="1179" value="SUPER" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="201" end="209" value="courses"/>
<opinion start="217" end="222" value="easy" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="234" end="239" value="they"/>
<opinion start="247" end="257" value="difficult" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="591" end="596" value="They"/>
<opinion start="604" end="620" value="respond quickly" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="591" end="596" value="They"/>
<opinion start="630" end="644" value="well informed" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="832" end="878" value="school programs"/>
<opinion start="862" end="869" value="unique" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="300" end="309" value="schedule"/>
<opinion start="268" end="273" value="like" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="552" end="573" value="staff professors"/>
<opinion start="580" end="589" value="high 90%" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="153" end="163" value="education"/>
<opinion start="128" end="145" value="can't say enough" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="64">
<text>
I am 2 weeks away from getting my Bachelor's in Business/Finance.
All I can say is that this school is a total waste of time.
The people that are in the classes are the most illiterate, incompetent bunch of brain dead zombies you'll ever encounter.
On EVERY &quot;learning team&quot; I have been in, me and another person were always the ones doing all the work (familiar story?).
Everyone else came up with the usual UOP excuses: &quot;I'm sorry, I had personal issues&quot;; &quot;I'm sorry, I had a family emergency&quot;; &quot;I'm sorry, I had computer trouble&quot;.
Basically, these are issues that you can't argue with but you know are total BS...towards the end I just completed assignments myself &amp; submitted the team papers with only my work showing because I refused to have my grade compromised due to incompetence.
As far as learning, like other people said you really have to WANT to learn the material.
If you bust your ass and do all the reading, answer all the sample problems in the book &amp; are motivated, you will learn plenty.
If you sit on your lazy ass and BS your responses, you will learn absolutely nothing but you will still probably get an A...or maybe a B+ if you were really horrible.
Now that I am at the end of my Bachelor's program, I feel so unfulfilled that I am going into a (real) school for my Master's.
Even though I have a career and most likely won't need either the Bachelor's or Master's, I need to complete a real graduate school just for piece of mind.
This place was a waste of time &amp; I wouldn't recommend it.
I did learn about my major but only because I wanted to...the rest of the tool bags did nothing yet got the same grade as me.
Maybe I'm the sucker afterall...
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="132" end="139" value="people"/>
<opinion start="176" end="187" value="illiterate" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1499" end="1505" value="place"/>
<opinion start="1511" end="1525" value="waste of time" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="94" end="101" value="school"/>
<opinion start="112" end="126" value="waste of time" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1236" end="1255" value="Bachelor's program"/>
<opinion start="1267" end="1279" value="unfulfilled" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="132" end="139" value="people"/>
<opinion start="210" end="229" value="brain dead zombies" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1547" end="1550" value="it"/>
<opinion start="1537" end="1547" value="recommend" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="132" end="139" value="people"/>
<opinion start="189" end="201" value="incompetent" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="65">
<text>
I am now a senior with St. Leo and I don't have any complaints.
You never have to be online at any certain time, the amount of work for the most part is not overwhelming, and yet you learn.
Because you have to maintain self discipline it causes you to learn more.
All tests are open book so that makes it easier.
The teachers are very helpful, and the staff is, as well.
I would strongly recommend St. Leo
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="23" end="32" value="St . Leo"/>
<opinion start="53" end="64" value="complaints" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="274" end="280" value="tests"/>
<opinion start="311" end="318" value="easier" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="324" end="366" value="teachers staff"/>
<opinion start="342" end="350" value="helpful" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="130" end="135" value="work"/>
<opinion start="160" end="173" value="overwhelming" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="408" end="417" value="St . Leo"/>
<opinion start="398" end="408" value="recommend" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="66">
<text>
UOP will accept anybody, regardless of their reading/ writing ability etc. Whereas, a traditional or even a community college always has some type of placement exams to see where you stand.
UOP is just in it for the money so they will accept anyone.
I took some classes there and was appalled at how some of the students in my &quot;class&quot; could not even write a sentence correctly.
If you want a degree just to say you have one, and want to pay big bucks for it, this is the place for you.
However, if you want any type of actual education, stay away.
UOP is a joke!
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="562" end="566" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="571" end="576" value="joke" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="194" end="198" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="201" end="226" value="just in it for the money" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="317" end="326" value="students"/>
<opinion start="289" end="298" value="appalled" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="469" end="474" value="this"/>
<opinion start="474" end="487" value="is the place" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="194" end="198" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="234" end="253" value="will accept anyone" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="0" end="4" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="4" end="24" value="will accept anybody" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="67">
<text>
My experience at DeVry was one that I would not go through again if I had a second chance.
I would advise those thinking of going to DeVry to do their research on the school first before putting thousands of dollars into DeVry's pockets.
Here's a quick rundown of my experience: 1) I had no problem with financial aid, cuz I figured, if DeVry wanted its money they would do everything in their power to get me the loans and grants I needed to pay them... which they did.
2) The majority of the classes in my particular field, Electronics Engineering Technology, were lacking competent, motivated professors.
The quizzes and tests they give were mostly open book and open notes with questions that were the same as the ones on your notes or book, or very similar to them.
All you had to do was replace old numbers with new ones and you got yourself an A. There were some professors who cared, but not too many.
I would say that the general ed.
professors cared more than the professors in my major.
But what good is that if you want to learn electronics.
There were professors I had who talked bad about DeVry during class, that's when I knew how big of a mistake it was to go to DeVry.
I had no choice, but to stay.
I was getting old and going to a regular college would take too many years.
That's an upside to DeVry, if you pass all your classes you'll be out in 3 years or less, depending on your degree.
3) I graduated DeVry Magna Cum Laude, which, if DeVry was tougher on their curriculum and not have professors who give easy As, I can say, I would never have gotten.
I would rather have an average GPA and good intruction, rather than a high one and not learn as much as I should have considering the cost of the school.
Maybe I didn't put enough effort into learning as much as I could.
But imagine what my GPA would of been if I did... 4.0?
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1541" end="1552" value="professors"/>
<opinion start="1561" end="1569" value="easy As" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="3" end="14" value="experience"/>
<opinion start="38" end="65" value="would not go through again" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="308" end="322" value="financial aid"/>
<opinion start="295" end="303" value="problem" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="1088" end="1099" value="professors"/>
<topic start="1126" end="1132" value="DeVry"/>
<opinion start="1109" end="1120" value="talked bad" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1340" end="1346" value="DeVry"/>
<opinion start="1330" end="1337" value="upside" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="610" end="621" value="professors"/>
<opinion start="600" end="610" value="motivated" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="610" end="621" value="professors"/>
<opinion start="588" end="598" value="competent" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1203" end="1209" value="DeVry"/>
<opinion start="1179" end="1187" value="mistake" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="68">
<text>
Up until now I was a big advocate of the way in which CTU finally started to get there act together.
However, recently in an attempt to pocket more money they have now switched all the students books to e-books.
They still charge the student the same cost as it would be for a hard cover.
Problem is this, half the time the books are not avaliable, you need to login everytime you need the books and half the chapters are missing.


The other change is these so called &quot;Knowledge tests&quot;.
These exams now are injected after each assighment.
They are tests that are suppose to test your knowledge of the topics discussed.
'NOT TRUE&quot; you will not get above a D+ on these tests.
They typically ask you questions that are not in the books, not in any of the teachings or anywhere in CTU's library.


CTU was on the right track but have now gone down hill.
Chatting with other students, many have intentions of dropping out to pursue other university's.
CTU gets a huge amount of money and one has to ask for what.?

If your considering a online college, I would advise you to stay away from CTU, too many changes that are not for the good of the student but for the college to make more profit.
Sometimes I think they have these tests so that students flunk and then have to pay to take the course again.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1118" end="1126" value="changes"/>
<opinion start="1139" end="1167" value="for the good of the student" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="807" end="811" value="CTU"/>
<opinion start="847" end="862" value="gone down hill" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1118" end="1126" value="changes"/>
<opinion start="1109" end="1118" value="too many" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="329" end="402" value="books books"/>
<opinion start="293" end="301" value="Problem" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="69">
<text>
Capella ROCKS!!!! Take a class.
You will not be disappointed.
http://www.capella.edu
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="0" end="8" value="Capella"/>
<opinion start="8" end="14" value="ROCKS" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="70">
<text>
I've been in the executive MBA program at CTU for over a year.
It's a great program.
I've learned a lot.
It is fast-paced and rigorous, but good material that has helped me already in the business world.
I went to one of the best private universities in the country for my B.A. At both schools I've had good and bad professors.
And at both schools, I've got out of the classes what I put into them.
This may be even truer with online classes.
Yes CTU is expensive.
But, so are most other MBA programs.
If they aren't expensive, I'd be worried about their quality.
The text books have been good but again, some better than others.
Online is not the way for everyone.
You have to be motivated to read and study on your own.
You have to be able to figure things out on your own mostly.
Im now approaching the end of my MBA program with CTU.
Im very pleased with the course.
The virtual campus and classroom portal have been great.
The classes have been challenging and Ive learned a lot.
Despite being online and not a traditional campus, Ive actually made friends with other students through small group projects and discussion boards.
After everything is said and done, I think that the things Ive learned have helped me to do my job better, and that was the main purpose of my degree.
I wanted to sharpen my business skills through this MBA program and ultimately amplify my career as Offsprings Vice President of Business Development.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="322" end="333" value="professors"/>
<opinion start="318" end="322" value="bad" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="957" end="965" value="classes"/>
<opinion start="975" end="987" value="challenging" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="583" end="594" value="text books"/>
<opinion start="604" end="609" value="good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="886" end="893" value="course"/>
<opinion start="869" end="877" value="pleased" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="149" end="158" value="material"/>
<opinion start="144" end="149" value="good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="322" end="333" value="professors"/>
<opinion start="309" end="314" value="good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="899" end="935" value="classroom portal  virtual campus"/>
<opinion start="945" end="951" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="77" end="85" value="program"/>
<opinion start="71" end="77" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="457" end="461" value="CTU"/>
<opinion start="464" end="474" value="expensive" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="108" end="111" value="It"/>
<opinion start="129" end="138" value="rigorous" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="108" end="111" value="It"/>
<opinion start="114" end="125" value="fast-paced" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="71">
<text>
I enjoyed most of the classes, except I had one professor who accused me, without proof and justification, of plagarism.
I guess this can happen.
No apology was given and I ended taking an F, after having close to a 3.8 GPA.
This was a mess.
My advisor was horrible, she told me what classes I needed and it turned out I did not need the classes.
I sent e-mail showing the exact comment she said and still she claimed not to have written them, this happened on several occasions.
I finally got a good advisor, but by that time my f.a. expired and I had to move on with around 5 course left to graduate.
On the plus side, the classes are easy becuase of the schedule and most of the professors are easy to communicate with.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="22" end="30" value="classes"/>
<opinion start="2" end="10" value="enjoyed" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="698" end="709" value="professors"/>
<opinion start="713" end="738" value="easy to communicate with" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="513" end="521" value="advisor"/>
<opinion start="508" end="513" value="good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="232" end="237" value="This"/>
<opinion start="243" end="248" value="mess" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="253" end="261" value="advisor"/>
<opinion start="265" end="274" value="horrible" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="641" end="649" value="classes"/>
<topic start="673" end="682" value="schedule"/>
<opinion start="653" end="658" value="easy" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="72">
<text>
I was really disappointed with the UMUC experience, both face-to-face and online.
There weren't many upper level F2F courses offered by UMUC in our location.
UMUC administrators tended to supply larger communities with more choices of F2F courses.
The equipment used in our courses was often out-of-date, as was the instructor.
The course texts were too basic, and for intro level students, I expected something more challenging form the UMUC experience.
There is no student community because UMUC is for career oriented people.
That means, it's about taking course to get a quick degree to move up the corporate ladder, and going home right after class.
There isn't much emphasis on literature or art or others soft subjects, so meeting people with those interests is even more difficult.
It doesn't help that the faculty and administration deliberately spies on students in student groups, plants information in the groups, and seeks to destroy the student groups when the messges get to negative about UMUC.
That is what UMUC's general cousnel did to a Yahoo!-based student group.
They are doing it again to other web-based student groups now.
There is in fact some truth to the rumor that administrators have been loose with student private identification information, and that it has been published on the internet.
There is also truth to rumors that there have been out of court settlements for wronful dismissals of UMUC employees, and EEOC complaints.
You have to know who to talk to or where to dig for that info, but it's there to be found.
I thought the courses would be more challenging, but because anyone can enroll in a course, the instructors have to dumb it down so everyone can enjoy.
I also don't like the fact that UMUC assigns instructors across multiple fiel;ds, outisde their departments to teach courses.
The end result is that we get instructors filling in for courses that ned to be taught, but who have less experience that someone normally tecahing that kind of course.
Anyone can teach anything at UMUC seems to be the policy.
As colleges go, sorry UMUC just doesn't rate very well.
Tell yourself what you like, but it just doesn't meet the high standards expected at other universities.
It's a quick degree for people who need one to claw there way to the top of a civil service-type job.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1764" end="1769" value="UMUC"/>
<opinion start="1745" end="1750" value="like" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="345" end="351" value="texts"/>
<opinion start="360" end="366" value="basic" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="35" end="40" value="UMUC"/>
<opinion start="40" end="51" value="experience" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="2060" end="2065" value="UMUC"/>
<opinion start="2065" end="2071" value="seems" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1591" end="1599" value="courses"/>
<opinion start="1613" end="1625" value="challenging" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="2255" end="2260" value="It's"/>
<opinion start="2262" end="2268" value="quick" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="992" end="1000" value="messges"/>
<topic start="1022" end="1027" value="UMUC"/>
<opinion start="1007" end="1016" value="negative" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="2113" end="2118" value="UMUC"/>
<opinion start="2131" end="2136" value="rate" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="830" end="857" value="faculty and administration"/>
<opinion start="947" end="964" value="seeks to destroy" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="2182" end="2185" value="it"/>
<opinion start="2212" end="2222" value="standards" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="278" end="286" value="courses"/>
<opinion start="296" end="308" value="out-of-date" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="830" end="857" value="faculty and administration"/>
<opinion start="870" end="876" value="spies" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="73">
<text>
I will be starting online classes through the University of Phoenix in just a week and I have to admit that I am very nervous after evrything that I have read, so I decided to do some research of my own.
My biggest concern was the way that employers would view my degree.
So I asked a career counsler at a former school that I attended.
( a traditional school by the way) and was told that many online degrees are considered useless by employers but certain schools like The University of Phoenix and a few others are just as respected as any other degree.
In fact they are becoming so popular that employers that dont consider aplicants with online degrees are having trouble finding employees.
I was also warned that getting an online degree did involve a lot more work and a lot more self discipline.
Its not going to be easy.
I emailed a staffing agency as well.
The told me that most companies have no issues with an online degree from an accredited school.
Infact there are a few companies that prefer them because of the self disipline that is required to graduate.
They also told me that there are some companies that are uncomfortable with hiring an aplicant with this type of degree.
Usualy because of a bad experience with one employee who ruined it for the evryone else, or the company is run by an older generation that does not understand or accept change.
They wished me the best of luck and told me that they would love for me to aply once I recieved my degree.
Ok, now that I've stated the facts, I'll give you my opinion.
If an emplyer would not consider an aplicant because they dont understand the hard work, dedication, and self-disipline that you put into earning your degree, then they are not a very forward thinking company and are probably not the type of company you would want to work for.
There are still some things that concern me, like the financial aid issues that I have read about and the problems with the team assinments.
But I have spoken to my financial aid counsler and she has been very helpful so far.
I guess I will just have to keep my fingers crossed and hope that i get a good team that is as dedicated as I am.
And If I dont then hopeful I will learn how to deal with a crappy team in case it ever comes up in the workplace.
My advice is to do your own reaserch.
Call or email companies that you would aply with once you recieve your degree.
Ask them yourself what there opinion is on online degrees.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="476" end="502" value="The University of Phoenix"/>
<opinion start="523" end="541" value="just as respected" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="571" end="576" value="they"/>
<opinion start="589" end="600" value="so popular" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="2035" end="2039" value="she"/>
<opinion start="2053" end="2061" value="helpful" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="74">
<text>
I am in Technical Mgmt at DuPage campus ; Illinois .No matter what you say Devry is a great school.
Yes it is expensive, but you get what you pay for...
I highly recommend DeVry!!!
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="105" end="108" value="it"/>
<opinion start="111" end="121" value="expensive" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="75" end="81" value="Devry"/>
<opinion start="86" end="92" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="177" end="183" value="DeVry"/>
<opinion start="167" end="177" value="recommend" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="75">
<text>
I enrolled in a degree program for a BA in Business Management.
This may be the biggest mistake I ever made.
I was completely upfront about my intentions to use my employee benefit to pay for the program.
Since I only get $8000/yr from my employer, this meant that I needed to stop taking classes in June of 2005.
When I sent an email requesting to stop classes my advisor suggested I could be covered by 2 more since I had some personal problems and failed a couple of classes.
So I was encouraged to stick through 2 more classes.
She failed to disclose you can't simply do 2 classes you obligate to 4 classes... this means I would pay out of pocket for 2 classes at a rate of about $2500.
To make matters worse...
I was told to apply for FASFA.
At first they say this does not obligate you to a student loan.
But somehow I ended up with one that got dispersed to them without my knowledge.
I am filing credit fraud against the school.
They say they have the money so it is theirs... and it's my problem how I resolve it.
Any calls that I make to complain are met with the response that I am the sucker.
I agree with the above sentiment... RUN AWAY!!
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="65" end="70" value="This"/>
<opinion start="89" end="97" value="mistake" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="76">
<text>
If you can make it through the first year, you will see that the lazy ones drop like flies.
My CET graduating class was three people.
And I believe the EE's had seven, and the biomeds had five that made it out okay.
It's not easy at all, but college isn't supposed to be easy.
Even if you make it out with under a 3.0 GPA, you will have learned a lot, (although there aren't many who graduate with under a 3.0...the professors are quite adamant about making sure you learn what is required).

I've attended two state universities and a community college and none have compared to the excellence at Devry.
Sure the academic department is a pain in the ass, as well as the financial department.
But where is it any easier?
Arizona State University wouldn't allow my loans to transfer from Northern Arizona University because I couldn't obtain a letter from the IRS that proved I had paid taxes for the previous three years.
As a result, I had to come up with the cash for that semester.
I don't see how that's any better or worse than Devry taking a little time to receive federal loan funds.
At least Devry lets you attend school while you figure out how to pay for it.

And yes, like any other secondary educational institution, they are also trying to make money.
You need it to pay for the computers, the school activities, and for the professors who have given up their jobs in industry to teach students what they've learned.
The professors are not only your instructors.
They are your foots in the door, your references, your mentors, and for some of us life-long friends.
I promise you, if you do well and work your ass off, it pays.
Because if you can prove to your professor you're good at what you do, they will find you a job, (98% of them do care).
After all, they have probably taught you since your first semester, (at least that was the case for the engineering programs at the Phoenix campus).

My data structures professor once said that teaching is the best job anyone could ever obtain because you have the opportunity to make a life-long positive impact on someone.

But if you're going to bitch about your own grade, then that is your problem and not the professor's.
You are the only person who can learn - it isn't the professor's responsibility to spoon feed you what you missed when you slept in every Friday.
And read a book, for christ's sake.
And as for &quot;vulgar reading material&quot;...get over it.
We're all adults; I would hope that you could find the underlying message in a book rather than harp on the choice of words and/or adult situations.

One final thought for the tlsail individual: Don't you think it's a little ridiculous to not hire someone based on where they got their degree?
Isn't it making an assumption about someone's intelligence based on your own bad experience?
Remember, Devry is an accredited university, and as such they are judged by the same standards as all other accredited institutions.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="609" end="615" value="Devry"/>
<opinion start="595" end="606" value="excellence" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="221" end="226" value="It's"/>
<opinion start="230" end="235" value="easy" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="626" end="705" value="academic department  financial department"/>
<opinion start="651" end="667" value="pain in the ass" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="77">
<text>
Terrible!
I am one week into an online course.
The topics in the class description are not covered at all.
The instructor simply wishes to post her personal accomplishments but definitely no lectures.
Although my week was worthless, I am being charged for the week, application fee and materials fee.
Please do NOT make my foolish mistake.
When I called about the misrepresentation of my course, the enrollment advisor CONFIRMED there is no instructor accountability.
Basically once the class is sold to you their hands are tied!
</text>
</sentence>
<sentence id="78">
<text>
I am a current student of their MBA program with a focus on IT Management.
I have been in the IT industry for 20 years and have run several lines of business for the various companies I have worked for at the director level.
I am currently a director, and do make a substantial income.
I did my research, and am concerned about credit transfers.
Especially, since I am planning for a PhD in the future.
I went to UT Austin for my undergraduate BS Comp Sci, and I can tell you that the quality of education between CTU and UT is similar.
On campus vs. off campus are apples and oranges though.
Without enough time in a day to run a business and go to school, I was left with no choice but to take an online MBA program.
So, far I have been challenged and pleased with professionalism, content, and quality of the program so far.
It's just like an on campus experience.. sometimes you get really good Professors, and other times you get people that should not be teaching.
Over all in that aspect, the two types of learning systems are similar.
The biggest advantage I have found with online is the pace, and ability to attend on my time schedule.
The lectures are interactive and recorded.
So, if you can't attend you can listen in later.
Ever sit in a lecture on campus and wish you had a tape recorder?
Well, with the lectures recorded online, if you miss something, rewind, and listen again.
Great feature of online classes.
There are some negatives, but they are minor.
Bottom line: I am getting my money's worth.
I have already learned a great deal, and the quality of my education is as good or better than my undergraduate on campus experience.
My $.02,
Cheers
Cory
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="846" end="851" value="It's"/>
<opinion start="851" end="861" value="just like" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="547" end="573" value="On campus vs . off campus"/>
<opinion start="577" end="596" value="apples and oranges" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="1541" end="1555" value="money's worth" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="1603" end="1611" value="quality" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="523" end="527" value="CTU"/>
<opinion start="494" end="502" value="quality" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="829" end="837" value="program"/>
<opinion start="782" end="798" value="professionalism" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="829" end="837" value="program"/>
<opinion start="814" end="822" value="quality" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="79">
<text>
Class material is weak, instructors worse.
Screwed up financial aid.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="25" end="37" value="instructors"/>
<opinion start="37" end="43" value="worse" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="56" end="70" value="financial aid"/>
<opinion start="45" end="56" value="Screwed up" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="0" end="15" value="Class material"/>
<opinion start="18" end="23" value="weak" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="80">
<text>
Don't listen to above post.
This school is all about the money.
The education is less than stellar for the amount you pay.
A community college offers better than this school!
Here you pay 6k a semester as compared to 300-400 at your local community colloge, 1-1.5k for csu, 2k for uc.
Overall most other colleges are cheaper than this school and offer you more.
I highly don't reccomend this school.
Most other private trade schools I would steer away from as well.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="400" end="407" value="school"/>
<opinion start="385" end="395" value="reccomend" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="34" end="41" value="school"/>
<opinion start="48" end="64" value="about the money" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="70" end="80" value="education"/>
<opinion start="93" end="101" value="stellar" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="81">
<text>
WOW! All the negative stuff about CTU, amazing!
Listen, I am going to give all of you the skinney on CTU.
CTU is part business, part college, as is any university.
With that said, you will get the sales pitch to feel warm and fuzzy about enrolling, however college has become big business and CTU is no different.
They want your money!
Does that mean they are crooks, no! CTU has a different pitch than your normal brick and motar, Brick and motar concern themsleves less with the student and more with the parents wallet.
Young children systematically fill out customary loan applications FASA and standard forms and mom and dad are hustled by the financial aid.
At CTU they deal with older students mainly on there own.
That's the difference the students feel the sting of payments and sales calls and bills.
CTU is accredited, thats all that matters!
Your potential job rarely cares about if your degree is from ST. Mary's school for the blind or MIT.
The only difference is highly technical jobs or important jobs.
They might care about where you graduated, other than that no one cares!
You think some social worker job in some city gives a damn if you went to So Cal or CTU?
No they just need somebody degreed to fill a seat!
If you are applying to NASA dont go to CTU! CTU fills a void for alot of older college dropouts needing to get a degree in a world that is flooded with schools sticking there nose up in the air to give the appereance that they offer something better!
Hogwash!
CTU is a good school, that's easy, accredited and fairly affordable.
About 8000.00 a year.
That's not bad compared to others.
If you want a degree that is respectable in the world of online colleges, CTU is better than most, atleast CTU is a brick and motar school and has been for over 40years.
They do hastle you about money, but they also give you a degree that is recognized by employer's that's all you want isn't it?
Go to CTU and don't worry so much about the negative comments, every school has it's drawbacks.
I once went to a school that had one room with two classes in it at the same time, I kid you not!
They had dividers in the middle that wouldnt close off the track and we could listen in on both classes!
So dont knock CTU, I drink beer and go to class, no bad!
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1305" end="1309" value="CTU"/>
<opinion start="1309" end="1322" value="fills a void" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="303" end="307" value="CTU"/>
<opinion start="313" end="323" value="different" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1729" end="1733" value="CTU"/>
<opinion start="1736" end="1743" value="better" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="325" end="330" value="They"/>
<opinion start="330" end="335" value="want" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="1140" end="1147" value="worker"/>
<topic start="1202" end="1206" value="CTU"/>
<opinion start="1164" end="1177" value="gives a damn" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="111" end="115" value="CTU"/>
<opinion start="149" end="159" value="as is any" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="386" end="390" value="CTU"/>
<opinion start="396" end="406" value="different" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1523" end="1527" value="CTU"/>
<opinion start="1532" end="1537" value="good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="35" end="39" value="CTU"/>
<opinion start="14" end="23" value="negative" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="82">
<text>
Okay, I have to chime in here, b/c I see a lot of negativity out there :-) I just received my Master's degree and this was the most difficult set of courses I've _ever_ gone through (bar none).
I found the required discussion/participation in class very rewarding, as NO ONE can sit in the back of the class in this type of venue.
It is imperative (to your grade) that you participate in discussions; there is a lot of knowledge and experience imparted in these discussions; much more so than I would have received in a traditional brick and mortar classroom setting.
Why?
For one (that I'd noticed when we all got to Commencement) is that most people were older than the typical Master's students at a B&amp;M at a University campus.
A lot of these people are out in their field working already with a lot of real-world experience to give to the class.
This is just one of the values of UoP that I've gained.
Some of their stories and experiences (and the personalities themselves!) I would have never met in my local University setting (even though many of those people may have been from other parts of the country/world, too).
The amount of writing that one is required to do is also quite a bit more than a traditional school setting (well, let's put it into papers/week count, because I'm sure that a traditional Master's program probably has one writing quite a few papers, as well).
However, within the typical 6 week course, I'd say there were the 3-5 500 word essays (the DQs) per week, the 1000-2000 word essays per week, and the mega paper/presentation (5000 words/lots of slides) at the end.
On top of this was the 50+ pages (or so) to read in our book, articles from the rEsource, and anything else that we could cull from the Internet, books, and articles from magazines, etc.
All in all, I feel that there was a lot of work and if you could keep up with it, great, if not, you ended up complaining a lot about it on websites, stating that UoP was not a very good University or some such nonsense.
I will agree, however, that some of the difficulties that people have expressed with the Learning Teams are true (I experienced that throughout my classes).
However, as a Master's candidate, you must recognize the fact that there will be people in your life who are going to fail and they will most likely be right next to you.
The solution?
Prepare!
When you see a big assignment coming your way, just assume that _you_ will be the one who will handle the whole thing and when people step in to help out, all the better.
You must be proactive and step up to the plate with keeping up the work.
Otherwise, it won't get done.
Yes, this does allow others to ride your coattails, but I have found that those people did not graduate, either.
I went through the entire program knowing that I was honest about my work and turning it in on time (and collaborating when/if necessary).
The one and only time that I let others lead (my very last class) was the time that things slid until the very last moment.
I agree that there is a somewhat inherent flaw in the Learning Team approach, but in the long term, the stragglers will not come out ahead, as they will not succeed.
This *is* how it is in real life anyway (these folks get fired, can't achieve, etc), so why should it bother you, if you are a success?
David M. Patterson, UoP MSCIS, 2005
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="221" end="246" value="discussion/participation"/>
<opinion start="260" end="270" value="rewarding" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="1948" end="1951" value="up"/>
<topic start="2013" end="2017" value="not"/>
<opinion start="2040" end="2043" value="or" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="145" end="160" value="set of courses"/>
<opinion start="135" end="145" value="difficult" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="2170" end="2179" value="are true"/>
<opinion start="2124" end="2131" value="people" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="3159" end="3170" value="approach ,"/>
<opinion start="3138" end="3145" value="in the" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="911" end="916" value="I've"/>
<opinion start="902" end="906" value="UoP" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="83">
<text>
Devry!? what the hell was i thinking ?I graduate in Febuary and I felt I paid to much for a high school diploma.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="106" end="114" value="diploma"/>
<opinion start="94" end="106" value="high school" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="106" end="114" value="diploma"/>
<opinion start="75" end="88" value="paid to much" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="84">
<text>
Education is what you put into it and the UOP is no different.
Some people need their hand held and will not do well in an independent environment.
What ever the UOP lacks in interaction, it makes up for in developing discipine, leadership and planning skills.
All undergrad degrees are about accomplishing goals and the UOP helps people achieve those goals just as much as any other school.
I have over 70 hours at &quot;regualr&quot; Universities and have found that UOP classes are just as challenging and provide the student with just as much opportunity to learn.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="164" end="168" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="194" end="207" value="makes up for" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="326" end="330" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="330" end="336" value="helps" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="467" end="471" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="491" end="503" value="challenging" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="42" end="46" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="52" end="62" value="different" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="85">
<text>
I recieved my Bachelors in Software Engineering last fall.
Never opened a single book they sent me and they were never even referenced by instructors.
In fact, half the time the instructors told us to disregard them.
I graduated with a 3.79 GPA.
I don't feel I really learned all that much as every assignment I did was done with info off the net and I probably only listened to half a dozen chats.
Chats tended to be worthless drivel of some instructor simply reading out of a book or off slides.
I've had to go back and use the books I was sent and complete the projects in them on my own time to truly feel that I earned the degree on my wall.
Its an easy A no matter what you are told, but if you really put effort into it you can learn.
It's just sad that you can't get the degree for a whole lot less money.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="662" end="667" value="easy" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="259" end="264" value="feel" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="405" end="411" value="Chats"/>
<opinion start="424" end="441" value="worthless drivel" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="762" end="766" value="sad" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="86">
<text>
I was one of the early graduates of the UoPhx Online Program back in 1999.
I started the 15-course Masters of Computer Science Program in early 1997 a few months before my first son was born.
At the time I had a BS in Mechanical Engineering from CalPoly and was working full time as an engineer to support my wife and pay the mortgage.
Back then we did not have broadband connections and the entire Online Campus required everyone to use a dial-up modem to connect and exchange information.
The Online Program made for great practical sense given my wife's pregnancy and time constraints.
I must admit that I had my doubts during the first couple of classes.
The use of teams with members scattered all over the globe made for some long nights and difficult coordination to complete the class assignments.
I also felt that some members were not pulling their weight.
In retrospect, the entire experience mirrored real experiences in work and life.
By the third and fourth classes I had hooked up with a core group of students who were also taking the program seriously.
Many others had dropped out by that time too.
The MSCIS program was probably one of the most intense learning experiences I've ever had.
Each class was six weeks long and consisted of group discussions that had required relevant DAILY participation in addition to lengthy textbooks, weekly college-level papers of at least 2000 words along with footnotes and mandatory formats.
The final projects usually were 5000-10,000 word essays that also required PowerPoint presentations.
The ability to communicate and write is ESSENTIAL for the Online Campus.
I spent many evenings at the PC way past 1AM.
This was not a program for anyone who wanted to slide by because the other students would rat you out quickly.
When I needed to take some time off after the birth of my son, the University was accommodating.
Financial Aid was available and was not difficult to obtain as long as you were diligent in submitting the required paperwork and followed up with your counselor.
In the end I completed my MSCIS in 27 months including a 12 week break to be a Dad.
I had a GPA of 3.9 for the program.
I was able to shift departments within my company and increase my salary by 50%.
I also had many opportunities and projects presented to me because I had both Mechancal and IT skills.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="499" end="514" value="Online Program"/>
<opinion start="514" end="545" value="made for great practical sense" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1701" end="1709" value="program"/>
<opinion start="1724" end="1743" value="wanted to slide by" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1569" end="1577" value="ability"/>
<opinion start="1605" end="1615" value="ESSENTIAL" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1138" end="1146" value="program"/>
<opinion start="1192" end="1204" value="experiences" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1897" end="1911" value="Financial Aid"/>
<opinion start="1937" end="1947" value="difficult" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="835" end="843" value="members"/>
<opinion start="852" end="873" value="pulling their weight" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="87">
<text>
I EARNED my BSIT from Capella a year ago.
As it has been the case with every educational institution I have attended, I had good instructors and bad instructors, easy courses and hard courses.
I remember there were a few courses at Capella where classmates actually went crying to the administration about the instructors being too strict or demanding.
I encountered several students that actually expected a degree handed to them simply because this was an on-line education and they had to pay for it.
They are / were usually the vocal complainers about one thing or the other.
In my case, I did or I should say, my employer got its money's worth.
Like everything else in life, expect to get out of it what you put into it.
No more, no less.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="250" end="261" value="classmates"/>
<topic start="314" end="326" value="instructors"/>
<opinion start="346" end="356" value="demanding" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="170" end="178" value="courses"/>
<opinion start="165" end="170" value="easy" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="250" end="261" value="classmates"/>
<topic start="314" end="326" value="instructors"/>
<opinion start="336" end="343" value="strict" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="151" end="163" value="instructors"/>
<opinion start="147" end="151" value="bad" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="187" end="195" value="courses"/>
<opinion start="182" end="187" value="hard" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="131" end="143" value="instructors"/>
<opinion start="126" end="131" value="good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="510" end="515" value="They"/>
<opinion start="544" end="556" value="complainers" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="88">
<text>
UOP makes the statement work at your own pace on your own time.
This is the biggest joke.
I am in my 3rd class of Masters in Special Education.
There has been nothing but problems with the Learning Team garbage.
I do not procrastinate and want my work done ASAP but when working in these groups you have to constantly leave messages for people.
I had a group that showed up on the same Monday that a paper was due and expected me to get it together.
I wrote the 2nd and 3rd paper myself and sent it.
All I was asking for them to do was make changes it they chose and let me know if the paper was approved.
Nothing.
I was told by a counselor that if the people in the TEAM do not contribute then you are responsible for finishing the paper without the other TEAM members names on it.
I did this and was pentalized for turning a paper in myself because it required the TEAM to collaborate.
I did not apply to UOP to do group work ALL THE TIME.
This is a masters degree program and every student should stand on their own two feet and get the work done.
It is not fair that some people put in hours upon hours while others slide.
I am tired of waiting for people to submit work and wait until the day it is due.
All I can say is that if you do not want to do TEAM work and stay up late just to get papers done because of other team members then this is not a program for you.
Even if you do the work yourself and submit it you will be docked points.
This in turn will affect your grade.
So technically you are damned if you do and damned if you don't.
I am in the process of looking into another school that has no TEAM work.
You do the work on your own and have 16 weeks to complete it.
If you finish before the 16 weeks you can move on to the next course.
This I believe at least for me is the best way to go.
If I fail it will because of me, with UOP if you fail it is because of a memeber of the TEAM not doing their work.
Points will be docked.
I am looking forward to getting out of this program.
Very Disappointed.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1357" end="1362" value="this"/>
<opinion start="1365" end="1383" value="not a program for" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1064" end="1067" value="It"/>
<opinion start="1074" end="1079" value="fair" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="192" end="206" value="Learning Team"/>
<opinion start="206" end="214" value="garbage" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="918" end="922" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="901" end="909" value="did not" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="192" end="206" value="Learning Team"/>
<opinion start="174" end="183" value="problems" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1167" end="1174" value="people"/>
<opinion start="1146" end="1163" value="tired of waiting" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="997" end="1005" value="student"/>
<opinion start="991" end="1012" value="every student should" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="89">
<text>
Maybe not everyone has had a bad experience with DeVry but I can give you two examples of why NOT to go there.


1.
Mismanaged financial aid.
They have this wonderful EduCard program they try to sell you the problem in my experience is they got it wrong.
They set it too low and I wasn't aware of it until I got nasty emails threatening probation.
Keep in mind no one had called me about this and *I* was not the one who set the paperwork to make it too low, they did.
I finally was able to cover the difference with a private loan and I thought I was golden.
That was until my last session with DeVry and they sent back my entire disbursement rather than use part of it to pay my balance thus leaving me in debt with them and no way to pay it.
I have tried for 3 weeks now to get straight answers as to why private funds were returned and I have been ran around the block more times than a runner at the Boston Marathon.
They changed the due date of my huge debt 3 times in the meantime and I am still awaiting documentation as to why they decided not to use any of my private loan to pay for my education, funny I thought that's why I had gotten one!

2.
Teacher quality could be vastly improved.
My last two classes were the absolute worst for teacher quality.
One teacher cut and paste the same comments repeatedly for everything, I often wondered if he actually read anything or just skimmed it and giving a grade.
Granted I don't expect a real life education but some level of interactiveness with the staff doesn't hurt.
The other teacher was even worse in fact any time you contacted him you'd wait over a week to hear back.
Work was graded very slowly in fact I was doing the final before the last two weeks had been completed which only hurts me, the student, in the end because I can't review it.
The instructor also couldn't spell or write effectively which was a major turn-off to his qualifications.
I had a programming class with no lectures which is always fun for beginners to try to learn concepts without any sort of interactivity.


With DeVry you get high cost and not much in return.
Most online institutions are considered diploma factories for a good reason because frankly they don't care if you are actually learning as long as they get their money.
The staff is nice enough but there doesn't appear to be much of a process for quality control at this school.
Another thing worth noting is at DeVry many times you will never see what you get on your finals because the instructors are NOT required to post them in your grade book.
There were many classes I knew my course grade but I never could go see how I did on my final which is something that is important to me.
After dealing with their finance dept.
more times than I'd care to remember spend your money elsewhere, the headache isn't worth it.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="2301" end="2307" value="staff"/>
<opinion start="2310" end="2315" value="nice" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="10" end="19" value="everyone"/>
<topic start="33" end="44" value="experience"/>
<opinion start="29" end="33" value="bad" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1831" end="1842" value="instructor"/>
<opinion start="1901" end="1910" value="turn-off" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1553" end="1561" value="teacher"/>
<opinion start="1570" end="1576" value="worse" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="168" end="176" value="EduCard"/>
<opinion start="158" end="168" value="wonderful" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="266" end="269" value="it"/>
<opinion start="269" end="277" value="too low" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="168" end="176" value="EduCard"/>
<opinion start="242" end="255" value="got it wrong" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="320" end="327" value="emails"/>
<opinion start="314" end="320" value="nasty" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1167" end="1183" value="Teacher quality"/>
<opinion start="1183" end="1192" value="could be" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1965" end="1977" value="no lectures"/>
<opinion start="1993" end="2011" value="fun for beginners" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1649" end="1654" value="Work"/>
<opinion start="1670" end="1677" value="slowly" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="2077" end="2083" value="DeVry"/>
<opinion start="2105" end="2124" value="not much in return" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="127" end="141" value="financial aid"/>
<opinion start="116" end="127" value="Mismanaged" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="2077" end="2083" value="DeVry"/>
<opinion start="2091" end="2101" value="high cost" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="2441" end="2447" value="DeVry"/>
<opinion start="2829" end="2838" value="headache" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1222" end="1230" value="classes"/>
<opinion start="1248" end="1254" value="worst" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="90">
<text>
I have attended Axia for almost a year (I'm getting an associates in IT).
I took a two-week break and I'm about to enter my fifth block of classes.
I did a lot of research before enrolling and UoP seemed to be the only thing that was going to work for me.
I have a young daughter and I work.
I work from home as a phone sex operator because any other job I could possibly get right now wouldn't pay for daycare and be worth keeping.


I, too was a little leery of UoP because of its reputation.
The more I searched, I realized that UoP was the only thing that was going to work with my current situation.
I figured that a degree from a school with a bad reputation is better than no degree at all, so I enrolled.


First of all, the enrollment counselors can be a little aggressive.
I sent a request for information online and when the enrollment counselor called me, she tried to sign me up before answering any of my questions.
This is where you have to be a little aggressive yourself.


The first two classes were horrible.
They were classes that just got you used to the online learning environment.
For people who are not used to computers or Internet forums, these classes would be great.
I found them to be a waste of time and money.
At the same time though, any college you attend, online or on campus will make you take classes you don't like in a degree program.


My academic and financial advisers have only changed once and do a much better job than the first ones.
Anytime I have a question they are very quick to answer and try to help whenever they can.


One thing you must understand about this school is that no one will hold your hand and make sure you do your work.
You must be self-motivated.
Between work and the baby, I have to put myself on a schedule so that I do not procrastinate with my work but it is well worth it.
There is a lot of reading material and sometimes the work can be more tedious than challenging.


Since this school is the only one (that I know of anyway) to let anyone attend with only a high school diploma or GED, you will have idiots in your class room with you.
I am not bothered by that at all.
Someone else's lack of education does not hinder my efforts in the least.
No one is asking you to be friends with them, just reply to their discussion question posts.
I have personally learned a lot from Axia.


The only thing I was concerned with was the reputation.
If this is your concern, there is no need to be.
Apollo group does have a bad reputation based on business practices but those practices have nothing to do with the quality of education offered by Axia or UoP.
I have talked to employers and looked at job applications for various IT positions and the only concern is that you have a degree.
Most of them don't really care where it came from.


If I were in a position to attend school on-campus, I would.
I wouldn't rule UoP out for on-campus studies either.
I would recommend UoP to anyone who needs to get a degree from home.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="645" end="652" value="school"/>
<opinion start="659" end="674" value="bad reputation" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="743" end="765" value="enrollment counselors"/>
<opinion start="781" end="792" value="aggressive" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="2102" end="2109" value="idiots" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="2652" end="2656" value="UoP"/>
<opinion start="2521" end="2536" value="bad reputation" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="197" end="201" value="UoP"/>
<opinion start="201" end="208" value="seemed" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="470" end="474" value="UoP"/>
<opinion start="461" end="467" value="leery" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1887" end="1904" value="reading material"/>
<opinion start="1880" end="1884" value="lot" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="540" end="544" value="UoP"/>
<opinion start="552" end="563" value="only thing" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1632" end="1639" value="school"/>
<opinion start="1659" end="1674" value="hold your hand" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1525" end="1530" value="they"/>
<opinion start="1539" end="1545" value="quick" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1410" end="1429" value="financial advisers"/>
<opinion start="1466" end="1473" value="better" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1017" end="1025" value="classes"/>
<opinion start="1030" end="1039" value="horrible" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="2978" end="2982" value="UoP"/>
<opinion start="2968" end="2978" value="recommend" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1220" end="1225" value="them"/>
<opinion start="1233" end="1257" value="waste of time and money" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="2921" end="2925" value="UoP"/>
<opinion start="2916" end="2929" value="rule UoP out" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1187" end="1195" value="classes"/>
<opinion start="1204" end="1210" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="91">
<text>
This college is the worst thing that has ever happened to education.
It is taking advantage of the poor.
Poor enter the school with hopes of earning a degree to get them better jobs and pay federal monies for it.
This college robs them of the chance by convincing them they are accomplishing something while it promotes cheating and nonperformance.
These people have to pay this money back some day and probably won't be able to get jobs to do it or be able to live due to high expense of paying the government back.
This college should be stopped before they cause bigger debts for the government to have to get out of as well as turning out uneducated people with diplomas that mean NOTHING>
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="20" end="32" value="worst thing" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="216" end="229" value="This college"/>
<opinion start="229" end="234" value="robs" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="522" end="535" value="This college"/>
<opinion start="535" end="553" value="should be stopped" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="92">
<text>
They have used one of the books that was used by a professor of mine from a SUNY school that would only teach with graduate level books for undergraduate courses.
I believe this university is of good quality and would refer others to it.
The only pet peeves I have is that citations should be taking more seriously, as some students have either not cited properly, but did have citations and group work is hard to manage.
Other than that there are no other complaints I have.
The only thing that I can assume is that some professors are leanient on citations is do to the fact that some students have been out of college for over 10 years or more, so they are not up to par with what should be done for citations.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="0" end="5" value="They"/>
<opinion start="462" end="473" value="complaints" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="528" end="539" value="professors"/>
<opinion start="543" end="552" value="leanient" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="275" end="285" value="citations"/>
<opinion start="249" end="260" value="pet peeves" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="396" end="407" value="group work"/>
<opinion start="410" end="425" value="hard to manage" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="201" end="209" value="quality"/>
<opinion start="196" end="201" value="good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="93">
<text>
I have heard nothing but good things about the university of phoenix online.
I don't know why people see online learning as some sort of lesser form of education, it takes alot more dedication, skills and intelligence to succeed at an online degreee.
I took some online courses before and I loved it.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="47" end="69" value="university of phoenix"/>
<opinion start="13" end="30" value="nothing but good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="94">
<text>
I took a few courses at Capella and found it to be a substandard experience.
Capella is nothing but a diploma mill.
Yes, I've seen some people complete both master's and doctoral programs there; however, these people had little, if any, experience in the real world and had very little to contribute to course discussions.
After my poor experience with Capella University, I would not recommend it to anyone who desires a real education - find a traditional school for that.
When you met a Capella graduate, ask them just what their experiences were before they completed their program - often, you will find that they have almost no real world experience.
If you want to buy a degree, Capella may be your choice, if you want an education, find someplace else.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="65" end="76" value="experience"/>
<opinion start="53" end="65" value="substandard" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="345" end="356" value="experience"/>
<opinion start="340" end="345" value="poor" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="404" end="407" value="it"/>
<opinion start="394" end="404" value="recommend" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="78" end="86" value="Capella"/>
<opinion start="103" end="116" value="diploma mill" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="95">
<text>
I thought Devry was great!
I especially saw a difference when I had to go looking for a new job in the past month.
Had an offer for $12k more than I made in my last job.
Big difference from when I didn't have my degree.
The professors were excellent as well the financial aid office.
On a two year sabbatical, I had to pay back my loan from Devry.
The financial aid person was excellent and by far the best credit person I've ever dealt with.
I would do it over in a heartbeat.
As a matter of fact, I'm currently attending Keller in Phx for my MISM and have been impressed.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="533" end="540" value="Keller"/>
<opinion start="573" end="583" value="impressed" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="228" end="287" value="financial aid office professors"/>
<opinion start="244" end="254" value="excellent" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="414" end="428" value="credit person"/>
<opinion start="409" end="414" value="best" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="359" end="380" value="financial aid person"/>
<opinion start="384" end="394" value="excellent" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="10" end="16" value="Devry"/>
<opinion start="453" end="485" value="would do it over in a heartbeat" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="20" end="26" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="96">
<text>
How very interesting that those students posting complaints about the UOP all refer to the same issues: FINANCIAL AID; Academic &amp; Enrollment Advisors; the unprofessionalism of the staff; the UOP being a degree mill etc.
They are all true.
Believe every word that is spoken.
Not only was I an online student with them for a little over a year, the continued turnover rates of these people in critical positions was a joke.
You never knew whom to call; you were never informed; the tuition per credit hour was just a royal hoot for the education being obtained.
Return calls, oh that's a joke.
I ended up leaving the UOP and had to enlist the services of my Congressional Leader since the UOP assumed they were going to keep my $1400.00 credited to my account.
Yeah right!
While I did receive high grades, I will admit, I did work hard for them - no doubt about that however, the deceitful, manipulative, greedy and darned right pestering practices this school used(uses) leaves alot to be desired!
On the other hand, WESTERN INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY (a newborn of the UOP) is no different.
They are just as deceptive, manipulative, greedy and very ill informed as individuals at the UOP.
I advise students to check around.
There has to be something better out there than either of these two &quot;institutions&quot; of ill repute.
Did I mention your hard earned degree isn't worth the paper it's written on?
Heard that DIRECTLY from an employer that said they wouldn't hire a UOP graduate if they were the last individual on the face of the earth.
Wonder why?
When the DOE contacts the school for information regarding a student and the school does not respond that should send up red flares immediately.
In essence, both degree mills should be shut down and made to return the monies they've STOLEN from many students based LIES, LIES, LIES, LIES!
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="957" end="967" value="practices"/>
<opinion start="923" end="930" value="greedy" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="32" end="41" value="students"/>
<topic start="194" end="198" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="206" end="218" value="degree mill" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="957" end="967" value="practices"/>
<opinion start="947" end="957" value="pestering" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1115" end="1120" value="They"/>
<opinion start="1132" end="1142" value="deceptive" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="700" end="704" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="1749" end="1762" value="degree mills" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="32" end="41" value="students"/>
<topic start="70" end="74" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="49" end="60" value="complaints" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="957" end="967" value="practices"/>
<opinion start="908" end="921" value="manipulative" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="32" end="41" value="students"/>
<topic start="182" end="188" value="staff"/>
<opinion start="157" end="175" value="unprofessionalism" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1322" end="1335" value="institutions"/>
<opinion start="1340" end="1351" value="ill repute" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="364" end="379" value="turnover rates"/>
<opinion start="423" end="428" value="joke" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="571" end="584" value="Return calls"/>
<opinion start="598" end="603" value="joke" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="490" end="498" value="tuition"/>
<opinion start="531" end="536" value="hoot" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1115" end="1120" value="They"/>
<opinion start="1144" end="1157" value="manipulative" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1115" end="1120" value="They"/>
<opinion start="1175" end="1188" value="ill informed" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1115" end="1120" value="They"/>
<opinion start="1159" end="1166" value="greedy" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="97">
<text>
I asked a Devry ECT advisor in Pomona CA why Devry was called a University.
He gave me a dictionary and asked me to look it up.
So I looked up 'University'.
I understand the definition but he didn't answer my question.
Why is Devry called a university?
Who grants the accreditation and which accreditation are the most important?
I wanted a side by side comparison but the advisor just shut me out.


If you're young, you have the time to go to a four year college.
Do that instead.
It's cheaper and classes won't be cancelled because no one enrolled but you.


I wish I've known this; I came from a foreign country and thought this was a good 'shortcut'.
By shortcut I'm mean learning only the stuff you need to know for your major.
Devry, Keller, Phoenix or some Tech schools keep calling me but I pay no attention to them.
It's a good thing I supplemented my Devry degree with classes from a neighboring community college, mainly math classes.


By the way, if you pay for a service, you are a customer.
Because of that you should demand your money's worth.
Don't let them treat you like a student; you're a customer before you're a student.
At the beginning of my enrollment, I signed papers relieving me of my ability to manage my account.
I was thinking, cool they can manage it for me.
But that isn't the truth.
They will charge you for stuff that no one really knows about.
I asked several employees why they were charging tech fee?
They couldn't answer my question.
I took it up with the accountant, he said it was out of his hands.
He said they have to change it in Chicago where the headquaters is located.
I'm taking an online accounting course from home and youre charging me tech fee?
It doesn't make sense to me.

The Devry accounting system looks like 1960's print out.
Who the hell use's that system?


More problems:
They couldn't get my name right, my personal info was never updated, I still get forwarded mail from my previous addresses which are a month late.
The community college I go to isn't much better in the way of equipment but I believe the USA is really suffering from lack of money for the school system.
Education should never be for sale in the first place.
Whatever you do, don't start at Devry.
Go to night school at the local community college.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1764" end="1770" value="Devry"/>
<opinion start="1788" end="1816" value="looks like 1960's print out" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="1856" end="1865" value="problems" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1730" end="1733" value="It"/>
<opinion start="1741" end="1752" value="make sense" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="98">
<text>
I have read all of you alls previous post and I can't ascertain so many negative responses.
I just completed my first graduate class - MGMT 610 (The Manager in a Technological Society) , instructed by Dr. George Ellis and TA, Dr. Patricia McKenna.
This course was challenging, up-to-date, and the text by Daft and Mann complimented the course brilliantly.
I worked very intensely for the A I received.
Dr. Ellis gave wonderful replies and critiques to assignments that were submitted in reference to the assigned work.
My chosen discipline and objective is a M.S. in Human Resource Mangement.
I really learned a plethora of strategies, structures, and approaches businesses, non-profit, and public sectors use, which fostered a better understanding of the way corporations operate.
Perhaps, you disgruntled students are missing the point all together.
The University is an open enrollment University, which will attract derelicts and people that seem incapable of academic success.
Look at it this way, if a University such as UMUC did not admit certain people, would a chance be given to them otherwise?
I look at it like this, as long as the college is accredited, I could care less how easy it is because I can sale myself in the interview for a position once I complete my chosen degree.
I bet you all don't have good interview skills to sale yourself.
So, you have to rely on a school name to get you hired, what a shame.
I can make a penny seem like a fortune.
I just need to attain a master's to open doors that would have otherwise been closed, an accredited degree which UMUC offers, will work just fine.
UMUC has a pretty good reputation from other post I have read.
There are mixed reviews from students that have attended UMUC.
All I know is, the first class I took I liked and want to continue at UMUC because the quality of my degree discipline has been good and proven commendable so far.
Let me ask you all this, If UMUC was &quot;too easy&quot; and the students and staff were beneath your abilities, why didn't you transfer real quick?
Do you all know something I don't?
When people attain a degree from UMUC can they not get a career?
That's all I need to know.
If individual's can't find work by obtaining a degree at UMUC, I am definitely in the wrong place, other than that i'm straight.
Reply please, let me know if folks don't advance or find jobs upon attaining a UMUC degree.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="439" end="461" value="replies and critiques"/>
<opinion start="429" end="439" value="wonderful" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1593" end="1611" value="accredited degree"/>
<opinion start="1646" end="1651" value="fine" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1869" end="1877" value="quality"/>
<opinion start="1910" end="1915" value="good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="1958" end="1966" value="you all"/>
<topic start="2006" end="2025" value="students and staff"/>
<opinion start="2030" end="2053" value="beneath your abilities" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1869" end="1877" value="quality"/>
<opinion start="1926" end="1938" value="commendable" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="1746" end="1755" value="students"/>
<topic start="1774" end="1779" value="UMUC"/>
<opinion start="1727" end="1741" value="mixed reviews" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1807" end="1813" value="class"/>
<opinion start="1822" end="1828" value="liked" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="306" end="311" value="text"/>
<opinion start="328" end="341" value="complimented" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1676" end="1687" value="reputation"/>
<opinion start="1671" end="1676" value="good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="610" end="617" value="really"/>
<opinion start="617" end="636" value="learned a plethora" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="19" end="28" value="you alls"/>
<topic start="81" end="91" value="responses"/>
<opinion start="72" end="81" value="negative" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="260" end="267" value="course"/>
<opinion start="285" end="296" value="up-to-date" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="829" end="838" value="students"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="817" end="829" value="disgruntled" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="260" end="267" value="course"/>
<opinion start="271" end="283" value="challenging" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="1958" end="1966" value="you all"/>
<topic start="1976" end="1981" value="UMUC"/>
<opinion start="1991" end="1996" value="easy" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="99">
<text>
I spent time researching and quite a few fellow employees told me the UOP was great.
Well, I have not attended a class yet, and I am thinking of not, tomorrow night is orientation night.
The reason why is because of the lack of response from the counselor's and how they avoid any questions you may have in regards to the items they are charging you for.
I was suppose to have the application fee waived.
Well, the online counslor pissed me off so bad, I refused to attend.
Then we deducted the application fee from my tutition fee and did not refund the entire amount to me.
So I spoke to an on-campus representive, who doesn't answer my e-mails/and a financial counselor who calls me at home when I am at work.
Now, I can finally see that I am enrolled in a class, but of course they want $1345 now.
There is a resource charge of $70.00 and I have to ask what that is for.
They were suppose to give me a credit for the $110.00 and they have not.
Of course.
I think that they are only after everyone's hard earned money.
They don't care.
My goodness, why would I need to take a general class when I already have a AA degree.
They offer same classes for their BS degree as what I took for my AA and transferable units.
I am thinking that I need to look around more.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="423" end="439" value="online counslor"/>
<opinion start="439" end="453" value="pissed me off" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="991" end="996" value="they"/>
<opinion start="1005" end="1040" value="after everyone's hard earned money" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1042" end="1047" value="They"/>
<opinion start="1053" end="1058" value="care" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="48" end="58" value="employees"/>
<topic start="70" end="74" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="78" end="84" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="991" end="996" value="they"/>
<opinion start="980" end="986" value="think" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="100">
<text>
Profit Mongers !

Degrees not valued by businesses !

Go to a state university if you know whats good for you !
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="17" end="25" value="Degrees"/>
<opinion start="0" end="15" value="Profit Mongers" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="101">
<text>
I have attended CTU online for two years and I am graduating in one week.
Online education is not for everyone, if you do not have self discipline or the ability to write well, this is not the forum for you.
If you want to be a doctor, lawyer or computer programmer this is probably not the college for you either.
As for the curriculum, it is for working professionals not kids that know enough to fill a thimble.
Most of the people that have a problem with CTU are too lazy to focus on the work and want more down time.
The curriculum is aggressive on time but manageable and achievable.
Pick CTU if you want a fast paced track to your degree and the degree isnt too technical.
As for the cost, what technology is cheap today?
As for the books, I have sold 16 of 22 books on Amazon with no problem.
My only complaint would be the group work; it is never very comfortable or productive but gets the point across.
Personally I am blessed, I make a ridiculous salary for a 30 year old with a HS diploma, I needed my degree to validate my rare experience.
My degree being in business is perfect for this forum and I can see where computer programming would be a challenge.
Overall CTU is a good fit for most of their programs, keep in mind with the price you are paying for technology, support, and convenience of not driving your car to a place where kids are hanging out and planning Saturdays drinking binge.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="535" end="546" value="curriculum"/>
<opinion start="587" end="598" value="achievable" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="848" end="859" value="group work"/>
<opinion start="878" end="904" value="comfortable or productive" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="848" end="859" value="group work"/>
<opinion start="825" end="835" value="complaint" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="535" end="546" value="curriculum"/>
<opinion start="572" end="583" value="manageable" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="535" end="546" value="curriculum"/>
<opinion start="549" end="560" value="aggressive" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="634" end="655" value="track to your degree"/>
<opinion start="623" end="634" value="fast paced" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1201" end="1205" value="CTU"/>
<opinion start="1210" end="1219" value="good fit" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="435" end="442" value="people"/>
<topic start="467" end="471" value="CTU"/>
<opinion start="454" end="462" value="problem" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="102">
<text>
I'm a US soldier in Iraq working on a PhD.
The program has been challenging but fair, with great interaction.
Like any other experience, you get out of it what you invest in it.
Good luck!
SFC Shawn Ambrose
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="48" end="56" value="program"/>
<opinion start="65" end="77" value="challenging" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="99" end="111" value="interaction"/>
<opinion start="93" end="99" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="48" end="56" value="program"/>
<opinion start="81" end="86" value="fair" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="103">
<text>
My experience at UOP has been quite rewarding both on a personal and professional level.
Here is my two cents with regard to the MBA flexnet program.
I graduated in September of 2007 at the Western Washington campus.
The majority of the instructors in the graduate business program were very good to excellent, however at any institution (top ivy league institutions included) there are bound to be a few bad apples and UOP is no exception.
Even in a city like Seattle, recently ranked as the #1 educated city in America http://encarta.msn.com/encnet/Departments/elearning/?article=educatedcities variation in the circles of academia is not uncommon.


Therefore, you must realize this fact exists at any institution, so grow up and get over it.
You must be stubbornly determined to stay the course and finish the program.
Yes, the learning team environment has pros and cons, but what learning model is perfect?
I was fortunate to have stayed with two members of my learning team for most of the program and one relocated for an outstanding career opportunity after about 85% of the program was complete.
I believe what set our team apart from others is newcomers had to prove themselves, otherwise they were provided an exit strategy upon course completion.
Sounds cruel?
Well, thats part of life and perhaps the individual learned something in the rejection process that is reflected in the working world.
Otherwise, you are crippling them in the educational process and the future challenge of life.


Additionally, our team kept each other accountable through constant contact and meetings.
If you expect the professor to manage your learning team, they dont have the time and your team is responsible to assume ownership.
Brainstorm a process and use it or you will be disappointed and discouraged.


One negative issue I have with the school is the incessant online marketing campaign.
In some ways potential students can view this negatively and may give the appearance of lowering academic rigor and quality, which is not the case in the MBA program.
Hence, I lowered my rating to four stars.


In terms of promotional opportunities, I interviewed for an internal position with my company and I received a substantial increase in salary (double digit) and responsibility.
After graduation, I still keep in touch with many colleagues and the student alumni association at www.phoenixalumni.com

Networking is perhaps the single most powerful tool one can use to uncover career possibilities.
http://www.careerjournal.com/jobhunting/networking/20080108-needleman.html


There will always be negative people, especially with the current paradigm shift occurring in academia.
This pattern is typical of new issues that arise with the advent of technology and education is no different.
Consider the evolution of other issues (i.e. workplace, political, economic) that have changed over the past generation.
Initially change is resisted, evolves over a period of time and eventually become a standard policy or procedure.
Furthermore, at minimum verify the online program is regionally accredited.
I wish you the best of luck in your future education.
My graduate education at UOP has served me well thus far.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="1940" end="1949" value="students"/>
<topic start="1958" end="1963" value="this"/>
<opinion start="1953" end="1958" value="view" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="17" end="21" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="36" end="46" value="rewarding" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="240" end="252" value="instructors"/>
<opinion start="295" end="313" value="good to excellent" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="2107" end="2114" value="rating" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="844" end="858" value="learning team"/>
<opinion start="874" end="888" value="pros and cons" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="1834" end="1849" value="negative issue" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="3224" end="3228" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="3242" end="3247" value="well" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="104">
<text>
Northcentral has a great doctor of education program.
It encompasses many disciplines and works well with my schedule.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="55" end="58" value="It"/>
<opinion start="91" end="102" value="works well" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="45" end="53" value="program"/>
<opinion start="19" end="25" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="55" end="58" value="It"/>
<opinion start="58" end="87" value="encompasses many disciplines" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="105">
<text>
Despite catalogue listings, diversity of courses offered is poor.
Books were community college level or lower.
UMUC staff unprofessional and unresponsive.
Instructors dumb down courses to allow many to pass course in the open enrollment system.
Psychology courses are of very poor quality by comparison with other colleges.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="29" end="50" value="diversity of courses"/>
<opinion start="61" end="66" value="poor" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="114" end="125" value="UMUC staff"/>
<opinion start="144" end="157" value="unresponsive" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="181" end="189" value="courses"/>
<opinion start="171" end="181" value="dumb down" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="261" end="269" value="courses"/>
<opinion start="281" end="294" value="poor quality" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="114" end="125" value="UMUC staff"/>
<opinion start="125" end="140" value="unprofessional" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="106">
<text>
Well,
i have to say after reading all the bad and good reviews about the UoP, i am just thankful that there is such thing as getting education online without attending in class courses, although being a working mother with her husband always gone(military)!

I am thankful that there is an opportunity for mothers like me getting a better education for an better future for my child and future child.

I come from a foreign country and working parents in my country can just imagen how it is getting a better education to get a better paying job!

They would pay the price in a heartbeat in order to feel they can be somebody someday, especially mothers in families who take care almost there whole life for there families and ending up having no education at all.

I appreciate what opportunity i can receive and i also gladly pay the price for it as well!

Better an online education that no education at all....
God bless
</text>
</sentence>
<sentence id="107">
<text>
Please don't go here.
They were or still is on probation.
They are also too expensive and not very challenging.
You only have to earn 3 credits in Math-Business Math.
You want to be proud in the college you attend and AIU is not one.
Save your money.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="60" end="65" value="They"/>
<opinion start="101" end="113" value="challenging" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="60" end="65" value="They"/>
<opinion start="78" end="88" value="expensive" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="108">
<text>
I am a Ph.D. learner at the school.
The school has a reputation for making students work really hard.
The thing I like most about the school is that the teachers force students to conduct research and formulate their own opinions.
They equip students to become not just learners but THINKERS.
I love this school!
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="310" end="317" value="school"/>
<opinion start="300" end="305" value="love" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="156" end="165" value="teachers"/>
<opinion start="117" end="122" value="like" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="109">
<text>
I hired an employee who was &quot;earning&quot; a Masters degree from the University of Phoenix.
This person was incapable of writing a coherent sentence or of displaying basic analytical skills.
Yet I would hear this person gleefully talking about the latest A she earned in her Phoenix course work.
If this is the academic rigor required by this for-profit school then they are producing a product from an apparent diploma mill.
I will never again hire someone who claims to have a degree from the University of Phoenix.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="354" end="361" value="school"/>
<opinion start="412" end="425" value="diploma mill" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="110">
<text>
Instructors are not consistent from class to class on requirements for grades.
You will be in class with someone who can't read and write English and you get held to a different standard.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="0" end="12" value="Instructors"/>
<opinion start="20" end="31" value="consistent" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="111">
<text>
I want to know if I should go to a community college or devry I don't know which one is better.
I am x-military so I get the GI Bill so money is not an issue for me plus I am in the reserves.
I want a program in CET or Game and Simulation Programming, I was going to go to ITT-Tech, but I heard that school is horrible and it's not accredited.
So should I stick to a community college and get my computer science degree then transfer to a 4 year school, or just go to devry and stick to their programs.
I keep hearing &quot;Yeah you should go&quot; and &quot;Nah, You shouldn't go its not a good school&quot;.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="517" end="525" value="hearing"/>
<topic start="577" end="581" value="its"/>
<opinion start="587" end="592" value="good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="112">
<text>
I have am half way through my second course with the UOP and I must say that it is well worth the extra money.
I went to the UMN twin cities for a year, and another online college for two years.
This has been the best experience, it allows me to work my full time job and maintain full time school status throughout the year.
I really feel the professors are great and readily available if you contact them.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="349" end="360" value="professors"/>
<opinion start="340" end="345" value="feel" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="198" end="203" value="This"/>
<opinion start="221" end="232" value="experience" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="53" end="57" value="UOP"/>
<opinion start="83" end="94" value="well worth" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="113">
<text>
I graduated with a degree in business (MBA) and I have to say this their faculty is top ranked.
They have been very supportive and attentive to my progress.
Unlike with more old fashioned schools, instructors don't teach as much as they facilitate information and provide feedback to each student's research and interpretation of learned materials.
They also help you tie all learned materials to your current job and work experience.
I've found that they are a great asset to network with too.
At Capella, financial aid was a snap!
The community of students is also awesome and I've been able to network with many of them.
The coursework is challenging and you will get what you put into it.
I loved Capella and I hope that they continue their good job.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="99" end="104" value="They"/>
<opinion start="134" end="144" value="attentive" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="516" end="530" value="financial aid"/>
<opinion start="534" end="541" value="a snap" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="75" end="83" value="faculty"/>
<opinion start="86" end="97" value="top ranked" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="639" end="650" value="coursework"/>
<opinion start="653" end="665" value="challenging" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="99" end="104" value="They"/>
<opinion start="119" end="130" value="supportive" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="560" end="569" value="students"/>
<opinion start="577" end="585" value="awesome" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="458" end="463" value="they"/>
<opinion start="475" end="481" value="asset" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="713" end="721" value="Capella"/>
<opinion start="757" end="766" value="good job" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="713" end="721" value="Capella"/>
<opinion start="707" end="713" value="loved" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="114">
<text>
I was just admitted to the Masters of Science in Management - Project Management program and my advisor was extremely helpful.
I know you can't please everyone, but I have had nothing but a pleasant experience.
The folks in the financial aid department were also extremely helpful.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="96" end="104" value="advisor"/>
<opinion start="118" end="126" value="helpful" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="218" end="224" value="folks"/>
<opinion start="276" end="284" value="helpful" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="201" end="212" value="experience"/>
<opinion start="192" end="201" value="pleasant" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="115">
<text>
So far its been two very boring years of my life.
I like nothing about Devry actually.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="72" end="78" value="Devry"/>
<opinion start="53" end="58" value="like" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="7" end="11" value="its"/>
<opinion start="25" end="32" value="boring" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="116">
<text>
I have just finished my course work for a PhD in Education.
I have two undergraduate degrees and a masters degree from traditional universities.
I have found the course work and research more challenging and of higher quality at Capella than at any of the other institutions I graduated from.
No institution is perfect, they are run by people, and people are not perfect.
However, at Capella you actually have the chance to get out what YOU put in.
I reccomend Capella to any highly motivated person who wants educational and personal advancement.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="469" end="477" value="Capella"/>
<opinion start="459" end="469" value="reccomend" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="164" end="176" value="course work"/>
<opinion start="213" end="228" value="higher quality" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="164" end="176" value="course work"/>
<opinion start="194" end="206" value="challenging" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="117">
<text>
I am a contingency recruiter in IT.
So I make living placing people in technology positions.
What I have seen is that anytime that a person has a degree from a &quot;one-off&quot; school - it is extremely hard to get them interviewed by hiring managers.
In some cases I have had candidates that have had non-technology degrees from prime schools and a technical degree from a &quot;one-off&quot;.
I can get better results removing the &quot;one-off&quot; from their resume than letting it show.
That to me is a tell-tale sign as to how these institutions are viewed in the corporate world.
</text>
</sentence>
<sentence id="118">
<text>
Hiya, mates!
I'm in the MBA program at Capella and all I can say is that classes are rigurous but you learn a lot!
If you are looking for an easy MBA, look elsewhere.
But if you are looking for an MBA that focuses on applied research then I highly recommend Capella.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="263" end="271" value="Capella"/>
<opinion start="253" end="263" value="recommend" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="75" end="83" value="classes"/>
<opinion start="87" end="96" value="rigurous" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="119">
<text>
do anyone believe that DeVry still stink and that no high school student shouldn't go to it if you do please respond it would really help.
</text>
</sentence>
<sentence id="120">
<text>
I was enrolled at UOP for a single class and quickly realized it was a complete waste of time and money.
The group projects were unbelievable, the subject matter completely useless, and the instructor was less than helpful, not to mention 2yrs later I am still getting spam mail from UOP.
I ended up going to AIU Online, which has a 100% better format and layout.
Unfortunately that completely useless class I took at UOP won't transfer to anything else.
Also UOP had tacked on an extra yr to my degree due to missing Associates level courses, however AIU let me complete all of the missing credits using CLEP tests.
Thanks to AIU I graduate with my BSIT in 5 more wks.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="62" end="65" value="it"/>
<opinion start="80" end="94" value="waste of time" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="409" end="415" value="class"/>
<opinion start="401" end="409" value="useless" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="149" end="164" value="subject matter"/>
<opinion start="175" end="183" value="useless" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="121">
<text>
UofP is an excellent school.
God forbid the people who complain about the school did nothing wrong to create their bad expericence at the university.
Where did your research in the university go wrong?
If it was so bad, than you should have dropped out the moment you felt it was going wrong!
At least than you could have went to your university of choice where I am sure your money will be well accepted there as it will be anywhere.
Problem is you did not have the grades or time to attend the University of your choice like Stanford, Harvard, Yale, ETC.
So, you had to go a university where the prestige may not be where it is as compared to the schools mentioned but to me seem to provide a pretty good education.
Get over it!! Put your bad experience on yourself.
Yes, there are those who help us create a bad experience but it is what we do when confronted with a hurdle that can change the situation.
Even leaving after all that is said and done is an option.
For someone to complain that UofP is a diploma mill who is now able to attend a top 50 university seems to me that UofP helped him get there.
UofP was so bad and horrible they stayed long enough to get their MS CIS at UOFP.
Also seems he or she did not have the grades before to attend that university prior to him being accepted by UofP.
More than likely this whiner found someone he or she thought was to stupid to go school, had a degree from UofP and decided to downgrade their degree based on this person.
Any way smart person, there are plenty of unknown small universities out there you can go to.
It is your responsibility to find out which programs are accredited and which ones are not.
Accreditation too has it's standards on who they accredit like do they have a big plushy office on the campus, are they allowed to have free meals, do they have box seats at the big game when they come to town?
If you did not see that one coming then you truly need to go back to school.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="588" end="599" value="university"/>
<opinion start="609" end="618" value="prestige" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1128" end="1133" value="UofP"/>
<opinion start="1148" end="1157" value="horrible" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="0" end="5" value="UofP"/>
<opinion start="11" end="21" value="excellent" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="1349" end="1356" value="whiner"/>
<topic start="1471" end="1478" value="degree"/>
<opinion start="1455" end="1465" value="downgrade" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="45" end="52" value="people"/>
<topic start="71" end="82" value="the school"/>
<opinion start="56" end="65" value="complain" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="989" end="997" value="someone"/>
<topic start="1014" end="1019" value="UofP"/>
<opinion start="1000" end="1009" value="complain" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1128" end="1133" value="UofP"/>
<opinion start="1140" end="1144" value="bad" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="989" end="997" value="someone"/>
<topic start="1014" end="1019" value="UofP"/>
<opinion start="1024" end="1037" value="diploma mill" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="122">
<text>
I'm about to graduate from Devry and I have had some issues I didn't like about it.
I'm attending the Orlando Florida campus, which has changed the curriculum tract for my major(Netcom)twice.
I found this frustrating at first, but my dean has been very helpful.
Although it is expensive the Florida Universities are not much cheaper.
I like the small classes and I have received good career advice from most of my professors.
Out of all the professors I had, maybe 2 or 3 were poor educators.
Personally I do not like online classes, but many students love them.
Overall I have had a great learning experience.
I noticed a lot of negative feed back from people who haven't attended the school, or couldn't hack the work load.
All of them have extremely poor writing skills, which says a lot about a person.
If I was debating whether to attend DeVry or not.
I would pay attention to posts by people, who have made it through at least one year.
DeVry is definitely not for everyone.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="357" end="365" value="classes"/>
<opinion start="351" end="357" value="small" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="53" end="60" value="issues"/>
<opinion start="69" end="74" value="like" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="357" end="365" value="classes"/>
<opinion start="342" end="347" value="like" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="666" end="673" value="people"/>
<topic start="651" end="661" value="feed back"/>
<opinion start="642" end="651" value="negative" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="490" end="500" value="educators"/>
<opinion start="485" end="490" value="poor" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="601" end="621" value="learning experience"/>
<opinion start="595" end="601" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="962" end="968" value="DeVry"/>
<opinion start="986" end="999" value="for everyone" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="203" end="208" value="this"/>
<opinion start="208" end="220" value="frustrating" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="397" end="404" value="advice"/>
<opinion start="385" end="390" value="good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="238" end="243" value="dean"/>
<opinion start="257" end="265" value="helpful" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="276" end="279" value="it"/>
<opinion start="282" end="292" value="expensive" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="123">
<text>
I attend DeVry Kansas City, and I'm leaving as soon as possible.
I came here as a transfer student with the promise that I would graduate in a year and a half with a degree in Biomedical Engineering, and that is not the case.


I started my classes here, and I've been going to this school for almost a year when I found out they didn't &quot;have enough students to offer the classes I need for my degree&quot;.
So wait...I'm supposed to hang out in college and wait for them to have enough kids to take these classes?
Any when I asked them what I should do in the mean time...and the adviser said to get a job.
Ok, 1.
I have a a job and 2. THATS WHY IM GOING TO SCHOOL.
I wish I could express how screwed over I felt when finding all of this out.


And on top of that, I plan on getting my PhD in Biomedical Engineering, and apparently DeVry isn't considered a valid school for that degree, so if you want to go somewhere else to receive a higher degree, you have to start from scratch.


It's overpriced for what it is.
Please, save your money and don't make the same mistake I did.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="841" end="847" value="DeVry"/>
<opinion start="701" end="714" value="screwed over" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="995" end="1000" value="It's"/>
<opinion start="1000" end="1011" value="overpriced" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="124">
<text>
The University of Phoenix for me has been just great!
I've complied with everything told to me (very important), done my own research (very important) and have never in my life expected everything to be spoon fed to me, so this school has been just fine in my book!
I can't go to school &quot;in real life&quot; because I am too far away from any campus (I'm talking 50-100 miles) and have a job in management which takes up 50-60 hours of my week, so this was the perfect opportunity for me.
As far as I can ascertain, stories of Phoenix applicants being turned away are just silly.
At the end of the day, if you're sitting in an interview and flunk it because you're not who they're looking for, then why not look a little deeper than blaming an outside source?
I wouldn't want to work for any company shallow enough to be prejudiced against a degree from a certain establishment over one from another, anyway, as money's not important to me other than the basics essential for survival.
Personally, I'm not doing this degree only to earn a higher wage.
On the financial side of things, I've been dealt with very well.
I've asked lots and lots of questions and been given lots of answers, and everything's been on time so far.
My financial aid was processed in good time, the grants and loans in good time, and my disbursement in good time.
The people I've spoken to have been friendly and kind, and knowledgeable.
The instructors have been mixed, but as others have said, that's to be expected.
You know what?
When I graduate, having done so much off my own back, I'll be damn proud of myself, too.
Put that in your pipe and smoke it!
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="230" end="242" value="this school"/>
<opinion start="256" end="261" value="fine" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1444" end="1456" value="instructors"/>
<opinion start="1466" end="1472" value="mixed" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="4" end="26" value="University of Phoenix"/>
<opinion start="47" end="53" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="525" end="555" value="stories of Phoenix applicants"/>
<opinion start="582" end="588" value="silly" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="125">
<text>
I am currently enrolled at UoP.
I am in my 6th week and I have learned a lot about Business Communication.
Before I got &quot;accepted&quot; my academic counselor went through the whole financial aid and student loan application with me.
Well, guess what???
Apparently I didn't get accepted for either.
Fasfa didn't send a rejection letter and neither did UoP.
The only way I found out was on my UoP website, where it plainly states that I owe $4,000 for 2 classes.
My counselor will not return my phone calls.
</text>
</sentence>
<sentence id="126">
<text>
HEY, I have a great idea!
I am going to start my own online &quot;University&quot; (those two words used together is an oxymoron)and become a millionaire like John Sperling.
Here is my plan: University name: University of The $50 Thousand Dollar Useless Degree. 1) Combine a few databases like EbscoHost and ProQuest and make them The University of Me&quot; Library...this way my &quot;students&quot; can retrieve useless, opinionated, socialistic, articles from which to complete their &quot;research.&quot;
2) Create some syllabi that will be approved by accrediting bodies that lobbyists have sunk their teeth into.
3)Get some half-assed computer geeks to put together a network and online &quot;learning&quot; system.
4) SOMEHOW convince the Government to approve financial aid for Associate Degrees to bankrupt 40 year olds that have been working at Walmart for 14 years--for CAREER ADVANCEMENT! 5) Open up a boiler-room sales office in each state.
6) Hire some circus freaks to sell the worthless degrees to YOU. 7) Hire unqualified, uncaring faculty to &quot;facilitate&quot; the tangential and inane discussions during &quot;class&quot; Sounds like a great plan....ahhh, crap, looks like The Apollo Group has already got a strong grip on my plan...
</text>
</sentence>
<sentence id="127">
<text>
I am currently working on my Masters in Human Services (General).
Great school, great education.
I want to get my PHD as well through them.
I had a 3.64 GPA and other options.
Why the negative vibe by some?
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="75" end="82" value="school"/>
<opinion start="69" end="75" value="Great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="208" end="213" value="some"/>
<topic start="75" end="82" value="school"/>
<opinion start="191" end="205" value="negative vibe" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="90" end="100" value="education"/>
<opinion start="84" end="90" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="128">
<text>
This is an honest assessment of the UoP: I graduated from the University of Phoenix in 2005 with a Bachelor of Science in IT.
I did the first 2 years of my Bachelor's Degree at a community college, but after deciding that I didn't have the cash to complete my course of study in this manner (traveling to and from school and working full time), I decided to go with an online college...the University of Phoenix.
To be completely honest, I was extremely disappointed with the University from many aspects.
The instructors give students a passing grade for a minimum amount of work, and are overly lenient with their grading.
I learned so much more at the the community colleges that I attended; the standards were higher, and the professors were so much more dedicated to being teachers - not just paid staff.
I would not recommend the University of Phoenix to anyone that is seriously interested in learning.
Take it from someone that has already obtained a degree from this institution...it's not worth the money for the degree, or the piece of paper that it's printed on.
If you want an easy degree with little work, low standard, and sub-standard assessments,(i.e. an easy pass!), then go with The University of Phoenix.
If you want to actually learn something, stick with a state school or the community college.
At least the instructors at these institutions aren't getting paid on commission, or by the number of students that pass their subjects.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="519" end="531" value="instructors"/>
<opinion start="607" end="615" value="lenient" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="850" end="872" value="University of Phoenix"/>
<opinion start="836" end="846" value="recommend" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1225" end="1247" value="University of Phoenix"/>
<opinion start="1138" end="1151" value="low standard" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="484" end="495" value="University"/>
<opinion start="462" end="475" value="disappointed" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="991" end="1010" value="institution...it's"/>
<opinion start="1014" end="1030" value="worth the money" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="129">
<text>
PLEASE, do not enroll in the University of Phoenix Online.
I wish I had read reviews prior to getting sucked in...
Sucking you into enrollment is just about the ONLY thing this school is good at.
I have taken 8 classes toward my B.S. in Business Management.
I will tell you firsthand this school DOES not care about your education...only the money you give them.
I attended Purdue University for two years, so I understand that going to a large college can sometimes make you feel like a number, but this is a totally different experience.
The financial aid counselors are completely inept at fully explaining my tuition to me.
I have NEVER been so confused by financial aid.
I have had 3 counselors since I started and lots of problems.
The only time I hear from them is when I owe them money.
Good luck trying to get someone to call you back any other time.
What they are doing should be illegal.
PLEASE!
I know you want to finish school and this appears to be a convenient way to do it, but you will only have more headaches, I promise!
I have been researching this school ever since I started having problems and there are just way too many students out their with the same claims.
PLEASE!
Do not waste your time and money!
I am now $15,000 into it, with one year to go.
I regret every minute of it.
You will not learn anything that you can't read a book at the library and learn.
(I only give them one star, because I had to.)
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1428" end="1433" value="them"/>
<opinion start="1433" end="1442" value="one star" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="556" end="581" value="financial aid counselors"/>
<opinion start="596" end="602" value="inept" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="882" end="887" value="they"/>
<opinion start="897" end="915" value="should be illegal" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="30" end="52" value="University of Phoenix"/>
<opinion start="9" end="23" value="do not enroll" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<opinion start="1225" end="1241" value="waste your time" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="177" end="189" value="this school"/>
<opinion start="192" end="197" value="good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1327" end="1332" value="it ."/>
<opinion start="1304" end="1311" value="regret" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="297" end="304" value="school"/>
<opinion start="313" end="318" value="care" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="130">
<text>
UMUC Online and UMUC in Europe have a lot of problems with providing F2F and online education courses, judging from the many student ratings here, on thecomplaintstation, and from internal UMUC docs posted to UMUCDE@yahoogroups.com.
I'd say there's a lot of student disenchantment with UMUC courses and programs, and UMUC administration.
It looks like UMUC could use a housecleaner for ineffective workers, and get in touch with the students who have posted their suggestions.
All the low ratings of UMUC F2F courses, online programs, and administration in Europe have got to be hurting business.
BTW, UMUC's hushing the student group wasn't a very cool thing to do.
I guess they deserve the low ratings.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="358" end="363" value="UMUC"/>
<opinion start="347" end="358" value="looks like" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="688" end="693" value="they"/>
<opinion start="693" end="701" value="deserve" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="508" end="513" value="UMUC"/>
<opinion start="497" end="505" value="ratings" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="16" end="21" value="UMUC"/>
<opinion start="45" end="54" value="problems" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="290" end="295" value="UMUC"/>
<opinion start="270" end="285" value="disenchantment" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="688" end="693" value="they"/>
<opinion start="709" end="717" value="ratings" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="614" end="621" value="UMUC's"/>
<opinion start="661" end="666" value="cool" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
<sentence id="131">
<text>
I am currently enrolled at UOP-online for my Bachelor's.
I picked UOP because I wanted to earn my degree, but I have to work and take care of a family.
I will be graduating in June of 2005 so I have taken many classes at UOP.
All of my teachers were excellent with the exception of two.
They responded with weekly feedback every week and offered great support and help when needed.
All of my teachers have pointed out both my strengths and weaknesses which help me at my current job.
I have received good grades at UOP, but I work hard to receive them.
I don't know how people can say they hand out A's.
It is a lot of work, but it is beneficial and I enjoy the experience.
The academic and financial advisors are not the most prompt in getting back to you.
I must say that is the major downfall of the University.
Like any school, you either like it or you hate it.
I attended a four year college and I didn't like it at all and the price was not much cheaper!
If you are a dedicated, self-motivated person this is the school for you.
If you need hand holding and a babysitter I would try somewhere else.
</text>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="878" end="881" value="it"/>
<opinion start="873" end="878" value="hate" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="863" end="866" value="it"/>
<opinion start="858" end="863" value="like" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="512" end="519" value="grades"/>
<opinion start="507" end="512" value="good" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="1038" end="1045" value="school"/>
<opinion start="1045" end="1053" value="for you" >
<polarity>neutral</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="292" end="297" value="They"/>
<opinion start="351" end="357" value="great" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="240" end="249" value="teachers"/>
<opinion start="254" end="264" value="excellent" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="579" end="586" value="people"/>
<topic start="594" end="599" value="they"/>
<opinion start="599" end="608" value="hand out" >
<polarity>negative</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="640" end="643" value="it"/>
<opinion start="646" end="657" value="beneficial" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
<frame>
<holder start="-1" end="-1" value="null"/>
<topic start="398" end="407" value="teachers"/>
<opinion start="463" end="468" value="help" >
<polarity>positive</polarity>
</opinion>
</frame>
</sentence>
</Sentences>
